Yo!
What's going on?
Guys!
It's been a week, actually, since I streamed last.
Exactly seven days.
Seven whole days.
I've been looking forward to this.
I've been thinking about Animal Well since then.
Mostly the graphics.
It's really left an impression on me.
Y'all having a good day?
Don't call me Olive Martini.
I've actually never had one of those.
Or maybe call me that.
Depends on whether or not I like them.
I'll let you know.
I don't have a favorite fictional animal.
Thanks for asking, though.
Or maybe I do.
I like monkeys.
The ones that jump around.
Swinging from tree to tree.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
I needed a week to just, you know.
Actually, it was like five days.
But like five days of just going out into nature and just not sitting in front of the computer all the time, right?
To find myself.
Which was kind of stupid because I was sitting right here.
But you know what I mean.
That was a joke.
Anyway, I went out and I actually fixed my diet.
I went for long walks.
Some running.
Bit of different things.
And it was really good for me.
I didn't snack at all during this week.
No snacks.
And I only drank water.
If you can believe that.
And you know what?
I feel good.
Shit works.
Ha ha ha ha.
I feel really great, man.
I did not hug a tree.
I only hug cypress trees.
And we don't really have those here.
Unless you go to a graveyard.
But it's kind of weird to be hugging the trees in a graveyard.
People will give you looks.
I can promise you.
What's up, Turtle Knight?
I mean, Turtle Kingle.
Turtle King L.E.?
Are you Tree-cist?
Yes, I'm Tree-cist.
Do you feel Copper-grade?
Hmm.
Maybe.
I'm excited for more Animal Well?
Me too!
Actually.
I'm always a little apprehensive with these platform games.
Like, for sure the graphics drew me in.
That was the first thing when I played it last time.
And, uh...
But it definitely won me over with the exploration part.
And I'm also digging the puzzles.
So far, at least.
Hope it's not gonna get too difficult.
A sweet spot is needed.
Yes, Mr. Ibrahim Dov.
You are now a potato.
I dub thee potato.
Don't forget you don't save last time.
I remember something about that.
I also remember saying...
Ah, don't worry.
I'll remember what I did.
Guess what?
It's been a week.
I don't remember what I did.
We'll find out.
It's not gonna be a big deal.
We'll figure it out, okay?
I just love that little stupid rodent.
With the fan.
It's so stupid.
Oh, man.
Who would've thunk?
I mean, if I had streamed normally after that...
Trust me, I would've remembered.
I would've remembered.
What's up, Mike...
Myselxo?
I'm sorry, I'm butchering your name.
That's kinda messed up, Cheezmo.
But, but yes.
Thank you, CJ Maxick.
It's good to be back.
I did have a great break.
Thank you, Mercury.
I really needed that, you know?
Sometimes...
You think you don't need it, but then you go out and you're like, you know what?
It's good to touch grass once...
in a while.
And not just think about...
all kinds of things, you know?
You just wanna...
relax your mind a bit.
I definitely feel better now.
Okay.
I'm just gonna jump into this, guys.
Also, I have a...
So last time, I took a note...
of some arrows.
So I don't know whether or not this will be a note-taking game.
But just in case it will be, I have prepared a note thingy.
Maybe we won't need it.
Maybe it's gonna be all in vain.
I only spent an hour on it, but still.
It looks pretty cool, but, you know, it's ready.
In case we need it.
Yeah.
So I'm excited about that.
People are saying it is.
Okay, well...
You know I have a steel trap, right?
I don't need notes.
I remember everything I see.
Don't believe me?
Watch.
I collected eggs last time.
That's right.
I got 16.
Times the detail.
Okay, that's enough of that.
Let's jump in the game, shall we?
Let me get a swig of water.
Yes, I'm drinking water.
Actually, it's sparkling water.
I couldn't make the transition, you know, just raw-dogging the pure water.
That's crazy.
Maybe one day I'll transition to pure water with no sparkles.
But this...
I love sparkling water.
It's so weird for me to say sparkling water.
I want to call it Danish water, because that's what we call it here.
Anyway.
Load game?
Let's see.
Uh...
Wait, 13?
Oh my god, did I not?
Okay, hold on.
Maybe I'm missing 3x then.
I...
I gotta be honest, I don't remember what I did.
Now, check this out.
This is my note-taking app, okay?
So, in style with the game, you know how you open this?
I made something similar, but like a little CRT monitor.
It goes like, whoop!
There's my notes.
You see that?
Whoop!
It's gone again.
How cool is that?
Tell me that ain't cool, hey?
Um...
Okay, so let me remind myself what I did.
Shit.
This is gonna be painful to watch.
Uh...
Maybe you wanna tune out for like an hour while I reacquaint myself.
Okay, so let me see here.
Uh...
Why do I see my...
Okay, so I have 13x.
Uh...
Let's see here.
Alright, that's how I did that.
By the way, I, uh...
I actually fucked that melody up.
That's not the right melody from Close Encounters.
Because I rewatched the scene.
It's close, but it's not quite the same.
So I actually messed it up.
But this one, I like...
This is my note now.
This is my music.
Of my people.
Um...
Yeah, I'm just gonna have to sort of...
Backtrack a little bit here.
I'm just going to investigate all these marks that I put down on the map.
Yeah.
So for example, this one I didn't do.
Let me see.
So I have...
Yo-Yo.
Weirdest item ever.
Slinky.
What was this?
Oh, is that the firecracker?
I think it is.
That's the music.
I think I have to use the Yo-Yo here.
Wait.
Oh, that's not the Yo-Yo.
This is the Yo-Yo.
There we go.
Look at that.
Okay, so we open this door.
I remember doing this last time.
At least I'm pretty sure.
Oh man, I forgot how gorgeous this game is.
It's really a vibe, isn't it?
So weird holding a controller again.
Oh shit!
Right.
That's a thing.
Let me destroy that, eh?
Oh shit!
I hit the one spike I couldn't hit.
Fuck.
Maybe I can destroy you?
Uh, it doesn't look like it.
Is he gonna...
What if I hide here?
Okay, it seems to be okay.
Shit!
Okay.
Not bad.
You found a match.
Okay.
I got two of those now.
I apologize if I'm, like, misremembering things here.
Okay, so I remembered this...
It's too dark to see the map.
Whoops-a-daisy.
Almost got me there.
I remember getting that chest...
from the other side.
Here.
Maybe.
Oh yeah.
Wait.
Uh.
Oh shit.
Uh, how did I do that?
Oh my god!
Oh no, it's a disaster.
There we go.
Yeah!
Look at that.
The planet egg.
I do remember finding that.
Okay.
Destroy these thingies!
Stelic mites.
Because they're not hanging.
Like tits.
That's that, like, tights.
Uh.
Okay.
So that one's gotten now.
I see a question mark on the right.
That's not food.
Okay.
Oh, this room.
I remember this room.
This room was blowing my mind.
Oh, I remember what that question mark is.
That's the room with all the different animals going up and down side to side.
Going for a hella ride.
Um.
Okay.
So what do I do now?
Question mark on the left.
Let's just investigate.
I think...
Oh!
That's right.
You were here.
Okay, so you're scared of me.
You like yo-yos?
You don't like the yo-yos.
Okay, okay.
Maybe you like it.
Oh.
Okay, you got scared of that.
Oh, okay.
Is there a specific melody you like?
Or sound?
Tone?
This one is locked.
So we need a key.
This is a phone.
Let's, uh, ring up the people.
Let them know we're safe.
And that we're gonna be home for dinner.
Okay.
So there's a swan here.
Not that it matters, I guess.
I remember the two, uh, marks I made on the right.
Let's go investigate those.
Oh, is that...
What is that red stuff right there?
Oh, that is a lit match.
I lit it already.
Okay, okay.
Okay, I remember this.
I'm just gonna go.
See what happens.
Look at him being hidden by the fog.
Or smoke.
Zup!
Oh, I had one job!
Oh god, I'm done.
I'm done.
Shit.
Oh, man.
Opens this.
I can eat it.
So, but what is the point?
It doesn't affect anything else on my screen.
So, it is just a shortcut now, right?
Wait, was this open before?
Maybe it was open before.
Whoops.
Um...
Oh, that's where I found the arrows!
See that?
In the bottom right.
That's where they were.
I arrived at that point.
From the right side.
I remember that.
Okay, okay.
Good shit.
Okay, so we have this...
place...
I do remember it, but I don't remember whether or not I did it.
Before I saved.
What am I using that?
Just destroy things.
Oh, no.
You need to...
Let me get off of you.
Just...
Can I even get off of you?
There we go.
So, that opens that.
Ah, okay.
Now we can...
Oh, no.
Messed up.
Whoops.
There we go.
Down here.
And now we can use this.
Yeah.
So, I'm guessing this is not persistent?
Then again, I did not save, so maybe it is persistent.
Go up here.
Oh, yeah.
I could have seen the chest this entire time.
I didn't even notice.
Promizek!
Okay.
I don't remember if I got that one or not.
But now I have it.
We're at 15.
16 was the magical number to unlock something new.
In the egg chamber.
In the inner chamber with the two eggs.
Um, now fuck this room.
This room is my nightmare.
We're not doing that room.
But can I get back?
Did I just flip the switch?
For no reason.
Oh, no.
It's gonna be this shit again, isn't it?
How did I get up here?
I think I have to flip the switch again.
Wait, how do I get up?
I mean, out.
I guess I have to go up here again.
Okay, so this one, I gotta jump up in between them.
I think.
Uh, oh.
Uh, now.
Yeah, that's how we do it.
Jump!
Oh, god.
Jump.
Nice!
Bro, bro.
Okay.
Flip the switch.
There we go.
Okay, good.
Okay.
Hahaha.
Now.
Um, so I did that.
Maybe I should make a mark for completed.
Ah, but that's dangerous.
Because, in my mind, it's completed, but it may not be completed.
So I don't want to accidentally, uh, rule out that area for the future, in case there is more.
We can try to...
Wait, what is this part over there?
That's the part with the elevator, going up and down, with the little, uh, creature inside of it.
That we could rotate.
There's a chest down there.
In the very center.
So how do I get there?
I guess I can...
If I walk down here...
Right, this place.
There's an evil animal here.
Fuck!
Wait, I'm...
I'm gonna just...
I can just destroy this, can't I?
Why can I not use it?
Huh?
Yeah, fuck that shit!
Hopefully it's gone forever.
Yeah.
No evil creatures?
Of the night?
Okay, I cannot hurt you with that, unfortunately.
Something's gonna appear here.
Oh!
Some...
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Okay, okay.
I remember this part.
I think I did this.
Oh, crap.
Oh, no, man!
No!
Wait, I still have my eggs.
Wait, when you die, you don't get reset?
Or...
What?
It's just a location reset.
It's not an item slash progress reset.
Interesting.
Let me get back here.
Oh, wait, how...
Dude, I...
This game...
I'm getting so lost.
It's incredible.
No, not here.
Fuck, where was I just before?
I went down somewhere.
Was it not right in the center of the screen?
Why can't I go down now?
What?
I am losing my mind.
I just went down there, didn't I?
Like, right here.
I just went down.
I don't get it.
How did I just get to the place I was in?
I am so fucking lost here.
It's insane.
So, I don't have to do all this again, obviously.
So, I came out here.
Right?
I did this part.
I opened that up there.
And I came down here.
And how did I get down?
This is so confusing.
Do I have to do this again?
Oh, this is not reset.
Look.
Oh, my God, dude.
Fuck.
Okay.
I guess we got to do this again.
Jump.
Okay, we made it.
First try.
Good.
Flip the damn switch, son.
Grab that.
And then up we go.
Okay, so let me take a look at this.
This is open now.
So, we go here now.
So, we got to do this again.
Oh, no!
The spikes are back!
Okay, I guess we can't reset that.
I mean, uh, we can't persist that.
Jump.
There we go.
Flipped.
But we already collected the stuff.
So, going down in the bottom right is not gonna do anything?
I guess.
Whoops.
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Okay, so now we're here.
Now we got to go back.
Oh, God.
I hate this room!
Oh!
It is my poison!
Or what do they call it?
The kryptonite.
That's my kryptonite.
It's this entire area right here.
Yeah, but...
Okay, I'm in.
We're safe.
So now I went down here.
Walked along here.
Oh!
That opens this part.
That explains it.
I see now.
But you know what?
I'm gonna go save the game.
Because fuck that room.
We're gonna call up the people.
Let them know that we did it successfully.
No more of that room.
We're done.
Also, what's up here?
Oh, right.
Okay.
There was nothing up there.
Oh!
Wow!
That is so fucked up!
Why is it doing that with its head?
Yikes!
Okay.
Now, this is where I was.
And I had to get upstairs here.
Yeah!
Oh my god, I'm good.
A bubble egg!
Fantastic!
That's 16.
Watch this.
I remember this.
Um.
Wait.
Oh!
Ha ha ha!
Fuck yeah!
Okay, okay.
Um.
Oh wait, this is not the spot though.
This is not the egg location.
Oops!
Shit.
Uh.
Oh crap.
I misremembered.
Am I close to the egg location now?
The egg room is over there.
That's actually not that far off.
I gotta go right.
So, a little down and then right.
We gotta say hi to...
Uh.
I forgot his name now.
Brian.
What's his name?
Oh!
There's a chest right there.
That's not what I'm getting now!
Yes!
This is where we ended!
Let's go.
Okay.
But to get up there...
Uh.
Come back.
Oh, you're not coming back.
Okay.
Hmm.
Boom, baby!
You found...
Pencil!
Oh, is that for the map?
Wait, what?
What do I...
Oh, okay.
Oh, it is!
Wait, what?
Aha!
Really?
Oh, that's cool!
I've been saying this forever.
Allow us to draw on the maps!
And they finally did it!
This is awesome!
Oh, that is like nails on chalkboard.
Why does it sound like that?
What is this?
Don't make that sound!
Give me a, um...
A fountain pen instead.
Or a ballpoint pen.
The pencil is...
Ah, just actually...
I just got...
Cold running down my back.
Just imagining a normal pencil on paper.
Ah!
That sound is just...
I can't.
That's why I always use the, um...
The pencils...
That have like the little, um...
Very thin pieces you can put in it.
And then extend it.
I don't know what the name is for those.
Stick pencils?
I don't know.
Um...
Okay, cool.
We got a pencil.
That's, um...
Now I kind of regret doing my whole note thing here.
With this.
But whatever.
I mean, I guess it'll be faster to write things on a keyboard than...
Using the pencil?
That's kind of crazy.
Um...
But the cool thing is...
Dude!
We can do this.
Check it out.
Let's see if I can find the spot.
Uh...
This is it here.
What we're gonna do...
Is we're gonna...
Uh...
Let me see here.
Down, left, up, right.
Okay, okay.
So wait.
What was it?
Oh my god.
It's flashing as well.
That's cool.
That way.
Ah, you know what?
This is probably shit.
I don't like this.
I don't like that.
But...
What we're gonna do...
Is do this instead.
Uh...
Let's see if I can do this, actually.
Here.
Then we're gonna do...
Zoop!
That little region.
We're gonna transition.
And we're gonna put it here.
This belongs to that spot right there.
See that?
Zoop!
That's it.
That way we won't forget.
Oh!
What's that?
Alarm?
Alarm's going off.
Uh...
Why is there an alarm going off?
Dude, that was actually terrifying.
Um, okay.
What do I do now?
You know what?
Maybe I'll try going down here again.
To the very beginning of the game.
See what, uh...
What's really going down.
You know?
And the darn part.
The down part of the map.
The beginning part.
Fruit.
Thank you.
The bird people are looking way more green than I remember.
Save.
Oh, bird song.
You must have missed something here, right?
Oh, there's a bunny right there.
Look.
How do I get up there?
I do remember this guy being...
Oh, yeah.
We can't throw the disc either because it breaks on...
On those vines.
Grabbing some firecrackers.
Oh, shit.
Wait, what?
Whoa.
Oh.
Wait, what?
Oh, I just found an egg!
Somehow.
I...
I just jumped!
Where am I?
Oh, that's funny.
Accidentally found an egg.
I didn't even mean to do anything like that.
Uh, wait.
Firecracker.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wasn't there something about lighting a candle here?
Wait, what?
Oh.
I thought I had full HP.
I guess I didn't.
Okay.
We're gonna be doing a lot of dying here.
Uh, oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
Wait, how the...
How did I even do this just now?
How did I get to that platform?
I'm so confused.
Oh, I went from over here, didn't I?
Yeah, yeah.
This is what I did.
And then...
There we go.
Okay.
I remember doing this last time, but I guess I didn't save afterward.
That's funny that I found that action.
Look at that.
Look at how hidden that is.
Could we have seen that from the map?
Yeah.
Kinda.
Oh, man.
Man, you really gotta keep a close eye on that, then.
Crank that turn.
Right.
In case I wanna...
Go back there.
Let's go up here.
Oh.
What the...
Sh...
I said...
Kangaroo man is back.
Okay.
You can't reach me, though.
Dumbass.
Hey, you like firecrackers?
He pooped out a golden egg.
You found...
It's shard.
It's shard?
Oh, K-shard.
I thought it was a joke on...
It's shat.
We're gonna call him William.
You know?
Shatner?
What is that?
What is that I found?
K-shard.
This is...
Part of the beginning.
Have I been here?
Maybe.
I honestly don't recall if I've been in this room.
I think I have.
The door on the left is open.
I'm just backtracking a little bit here.
God, I love this interaction with the lamps.
Right, there was something down there I couldn't access.
That's true.
I do remember that.
Also, I'm seeing a little path here.
There.
Right there.
That mechanic is actually really cool.
Great job.
Now, there's probably something up here.
If I can get up.
Somehow.
I'm also really looking at this room.
I see a potential hidden path underneath the basin.
To the right of me.
Let's jump down here again.
Something is happening in here.
That's why I have all these firecrackers.
And we also have these weird symbols on this...
I don't even know what to call that.
A mural.
Up there.
That's a bunny and a crab.
That's a bunny man.
A rocket.
And a...
Not a crab, but what is the other one called?
The one that is just like a crab, but it's not really a crab.
You know what I mean?
Oh, shit.
Eat that.
Have fun, noob.
Now, can I light a candle in here and stop him from doing those things?
Because that is very unpleasant.
We got four places with water here.
Does that mean anything?
Okay, now I'm back here.
Let's save the game.
Flopby disk that.
Okay, so I was that way.
Let's go back down here and check out what that was.
That should be possible, right?
So that means we just go like this.
Oh!
Didn't mean to do that.
Right.
Is this where we started?
We came out of this one, didn't we?
And then I went to the left, immediately thinking there was a secret, and I was right.
I remember this now.
But how to get up there?
We have a disk now.
Oh, wait.
It's not gonna come back.
Oh, that works!
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Oh!
Wait.
Music.
Dude, I forgot how I activated the bear.
I did something, and the bear was activated.
Why does it open menu?
No, I'm clicking the map button.
What the hell?
Let's put a marker here for animal.
Which was stamp.
We can do...
Oh.
I don't know.
Let's do love for animal, okay?
Yeah.
Love is now animal.
Because we love the animals.
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's four candles lit up there on the left.
So we gotta find more candles.
I don't recall whether or not I lit four candles, but I probably did.
And look at that.
There's little me's on that pillar.
Little versions of me.
Okay, I think we've thoroughly explored this region here.
Maybe we could look for secrets.
Does the map suggest any kind of secret?
Doesn't look like it.
No, I'm back here.
Okay, okay.
It's good to retrace steps here.
Wait, is that a safe?
Wait a sec.
What is that?
Circular recess.
Okay.
Oh.
Can I not put my disc in?
Or maybe the other disc.
There were two discs, right?
There's also the disc that makes the animal evil.
The creature itself.
Stop opening the damn...
Bro!
Okay.
There we go.
Here.
Let's just write...
Let's write...
Re...
Says...
Beautiful.
I like that note-taking system.
I'm a fan.
Okay.
Moving on.
Save the game.
Let's see where else we can go.
Now we're back in the beginning, sort of.
Whoop.
There we go.
Okay.
And if I go left now, I will arrive over here again, but in the top part of it.
What if I go up?
And we have this entire region that we explored most of.
Well, most of.
Oh, there's also...
Yeah, this little place there.
Let's try and go there.
So...
This way.
You know what?
Every time I see a telephone, I'm gonna ring somebody, random.
Just gonna punch in a random number.
Oh, that's right!
We got fish!
Oh, yeah?
I do remember this spot.
Wait, what?
Oh!
I never went here!
Oh, my God.
They are gonna kill me, I think, if I get close.
Oh, no.
Oh, that's creepy.
Why are these animals so creepy looking?
I still love them, though.
Oh?
Wait, what?
Is that water?
Oh, that's funny!
Where does it need to go?
Ah!
Up here?
Hey!
That's cool!
What a great mechanic!
The physics are out of control!
That's so nice!
Let me remove that before I forget.
Ah, shit.
I gotta get used to these key bindings.
There we go.
It's surprisingly well-implemented.
Oh, shit.
We gotta destroy these with this.
Nope.
Haha!
Nice.
I can...
How do I...
Jump!
I can't reach it.
Hmm.
Can I jump on these?
Oh!
Oh, they...
They get destroyed after a while.
Or do they?
No, they don't.
Only when you jump from it.
Okay.
But wait a second.
I smell a secret.
I smell secrets!
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
I fucked it up, didn't I?
How do I get up?
Oh, god.
Yes!
Oh, shit.
Oh, this is...
Confusing.
Oh!
I made it!
I'm so good!
I'm so good.
Okay, we gotta find a key here.
I also see stuff on the left.
I...
You can't...
Yeah, I see it.
I see it all.
I see everything.
Yep!
Oh, my god.
Oh, okay.
Vines are in the way.
Opens that.
Ooh.
I wanna just re-orient myself with the map.
So, we found a new area here.
I'm just gonna take a mental snapshot.
Okay, okay.
We got a little, uh...
Bubble region there.
Let's not forget that.
That's how that looks.
That thing...
Yeah!
I figured.
It looked evil.
The smoke effects are so good.
I'm mesmerized by it.
So, we gotta get to the...
Okay, that's easy.
Oh, but wait.
Now he's gonna be able to shoot me.
Is it gonna come back?
It's not gonna come back.
Okay.
But maybe I can...
Oh, that's locked off now.
Okay, it's not a big problem.
I see the button.
Sweet.
Oh, wait.
I also see a...
I see something up there.
Up top.
Maybe I go there first.
Shit!
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
We can't...
We can't die here.
Oh, okay.
I see HP.
Grab that.
Oh.
Wait.
I think we have to go up there.
No!
Oh, God.
Dude, this is not easy.
How the hell you can't reach that?
Okay.
Trusty disc.
See ya, bitch!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh!
I made it.
Somehow.
Run!
Oh!
Wow!
Damn.
That was scary.
Maybe I don't love the animals.
I take my love back.
Why are you evil?
Vampire?
Wait, what was the point of this?
I clicked a bunch of buttons and...
For what?
What did I get out of this?
I'm confused.
Oh, well.
Bubble time!
Wee!
Oh, oh!
There's something up there.
Maybe.
Oh, God.
Oh, it's open.
A mystic egg.
Oh, that's what happened.
Okay.
Good.
Look at me.
Spinning.
Oi!
I thought I could do some tricks with the skateboard.
I need to pick this up.
There we go.
So, to get up there...
This is how we do it.
Ai!
Yeah, dude!
Nice.
Buttons.
Oh, shit!
We need...
Button from the...
Oh!
Okay, okay.
I see.
B for button.
Very nice.
And that's blocked off.
Right!
This was the spot where I thought I could go through.
At some point.
I think this symbol I put here was the symbol for...
A wall that I think is breakable, but you can't break it yet symbol.
That's what that was.
How do I remove it?
How do you remove it?
Simple.
Ah!
Okay.
I get it.
Okay, so I think I know how to do this.
Nope.
Maybe I don't.
We gotta get up here again.
That bottom part on the right.
I don't recall what that area is.
Yeah.
Anyway, we also had a path down here.
And there's also stuff below.
You know what?
I think there's secret below.
I am low on HP, though.
This is a little risky.
Actually, you know what?
It's way too risky.
Oh, shoot!
Okay.
Whoa.
Whales!
There's whales!
With green squares.
Say what?
What am I looking at?
What's the difference between these?
Okay.
Wait.
I see a button down there.
Oh!
With a green square on it, too.
I have to approach that from below, I think.
There's also a door in the top left.
But...
Let's just calmly descend.
Ha ha!
So that's where they come from.
That's funny.
I love the animals again.
Look at them.
They're so cute.
You want to hear my song?
Eh?
There you go.
You happy with that?
I thought I could jump on them.
Okay.
Never mind.
Bubble me.
Die!
I'm okay.
I got it.
Oh, wait.
This is not it.
Higher up.
Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy, oy.
Oh, my God.
This is difficult.
The bubbles are so difficult.
Ah!
No!
Why is this so difficult?
Never mind.
It's easy.
Oy, I made it.
I made it.
Eat that.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Calm down, calm down.
Okay, I see, I see.
This is great.
I think we climb up.
Yes.
Oh, the whales are spinning!
Oh, it's a fan!
Look at me!
Hey!
Cool.
Oh, this is actually great.
Look at that!
Let me become buoyant.
Okay, I gotta get up there.
Oh.
Yep.
We made it.
Okay.
Those spikes look like they could kill me.
That's with all spikes.
You know what?
This game reminds me a little bit of...
Prince of Persia.
You know the one?
The very old one.
Something about the graphics and those white spikes remind me about it.
Remind me of it.
I should say.
I do see a little something there.
Hold on, I'm not being fooled.
How do I get up there?
Oh my god.
There we go.
There gotta be a little...
Oh, never mind.
Wait, wait.
I can just jump.
Oh no, I can't.
Yes, I can.
Look at this.
Ah!
Okay, that's a little too early.
Yeah!
Now, that's dangerous down there.
How am I gonna swing that?
Maybe I...
Do this, eh?
No?
Okay.
Wait, what?
Let's see what's over here.
I'll remember this spot.
Save the game.
Oh, yes.
No, no.
Uh, wait.
Okay, that's fine.
I wanted to eat first.
Okay, so can we destroy these?
Oh, we can.
Okay, okay, good.
They look different from the other spikes that we can destroy.
Okay, we got more food.
Easy.
Hey, sir.
Open your mouth.
You hungry?
It's a shark.
I can go down.
There's also a path on the left.
Let's keep this in mind.
Oh, that's a starfish behind there.
I saw you.
There's also an arrow pointing up here.
Is that a hint?
Or not?
Getting a little...
Oh, that's a spike.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
How do I survive?
I'm done.
Okay, I'm fine.
Ooh.
Very unfortunate respawn there.
What the hell?
I am in trouble.
Break it all.
Oh, secret path.
I'm getting overwhelmed a little bit.
Oh, god.
I almost just flew into that.
Yeah.
I can't get back up.
Let's go down.
Oh.
Sunset egg.
Cool.
We can be more healthy with our junk food now.
Allegedly.
Break them all.
I wish this was persistent.
Or maybe it is.
Maybe dying, you know...
I just have to not die, basically.
And now I'm back up here.
Okay, that's good.
Oh, there's a spike there!
Motherfucker!
I didn't even see it.
Shit.
Okay, fine.
Wow.
Why is the yo-yo so weird?
Just down.
My god.
Okay.
That works.
Man, that is such a secret path here.
It's crazy.
Oh, yeah.
We got that already.
Nothing over here.
Okay.
I want to break all these bitches.
Break them.
Yep.
Why?
What?
Nice.
It's actually so satisfying to break these.
The sound is so good.
Another secret path!
Well, not that secret, but...
I'll take it.
The question is, how do we get back up?
Yo.
Okay, we got a chest.
Oh, shit!
I knew that was gonna happen.
Okay, so I guess we're gonna...
Yeah, I don't know.
Am I fucked?
I did see another path.
Oh, god.
Ah!
I had it.
There we go!
Another fish in the wall.
Can I play you a melody?
You don't like the melody?
The bear liked the melody.
Maybe the animals want different things.
The bear likes music.
The fish likes...
I don't know.
Food.
Whoa!
Okay.
Wait, what the fuck?
I'm so confused!
What am I supposed to do here?
Ah!
Take me back.
Bop!
Where can I go?
We can go right.
If I can get up there, though.
Okay, I can get up there.
That's gonna come back.
There we go.
I didn't mean to do that.
See, water's coming down from above.
Okay, I thought maybe there was a path.
Lovely little region.
Oh, look at this.
Little effect.
That's neat.
Oh, my god.
Those starfish are creeping me out, actually.
Why are they crawling?
Shouldn't they be swimming?
It's an animal of the ocean.
You're not allowed to crawl.
Yep.
Break all these.
In case there's a secret.
I'm a whore for secrets.
I love them.
What?
Oh, spikes.
I missed those.
Easy.
Bop!
No problem.
We did it.
Oh, he's making bubbles!
I see, I see, I see.
Oh, wait, do I get hurt by the water?
Oh, I thought the water hurt me.
Oh, it pushes me.
I see.
Oh, this, this is interesting.
Go!
Oh, man.
Ah, now we made it here.
Okay.
Jump!
You found a bee wand.
Oh.
Oh!
A bubble wand.
Ha ha ha!
Cool!
Oh, oh, so I can, I can just...
Really?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I can't rise forever.
Can I, while I'm on it?
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God.
Ha ha ha ha!
Shit!
I'm so bad at this game, it's insane!
Okay.
Oh, I get it.
We need to use this here, of course.
Makes so much sense.
Thank you, Sean.
Oh!
His eyes turned on!
Uh.
Oh.
Okay, that worked!
Oh, we, we, fast travel.
Yeah!
Nice!
Hey, that's super cool!
Very nice.
Okay, that makes sense, too.
The fish is in the fishy region with the, with the swim stalkers and all the, uh, uh, sea stars?
Why did I have ocean, sea stars?
Is that what they're called?
What did I call them just before?
I forgot.
Ha ha!
Whatever.
Let's, uh, bee wander away.
Around.
Boop.
Look at that.
Oh, here we need to do a disc situation.
Interesting.
Okay.
I see your stance.
Okay, so we have a whale block.
Here.
Oh.
Oh!
No, this is so good!
Oh, I love it!
This game is amazing.
It's frickin' incredible.
The combinations are out of control.
Wait, I'm getting lost now.
Um.
Okay, we gotta turn this one on.
Somehow.
That's a fan.
Okay, I'm full on that.
I didn't check.
Ah!
Okay.
So how do I get...
Okay, I guess I can just...
Uh, not that way, sir.
Oh my god.
Nice!
So now I'm here.
Ah, but I see something up top where I was.
Oh shit.
Wait, does the water break it?
Oh, wait.
Is there a limit on...
Maybe the game is like...
Ah, ah, ah.
You can't...
You can't do that.
Okay.
Now up here on the right, something's going on.
Yeah.
A bit of food.
Aha!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, I see you, motherfucker.
Oh shit.
I think they break on vines.
An ancient egg!
Incredible.
Oh, didn't mean to do that.
Let me just calmly ascend here.
I want to go back up here.
Whoops.
Bro.
Bruh, bruh, bruh, bruh.
Bastard.
Okay, so you can't throw them into the wall.
That makes sense.
Oh wait, I can just go here.
Yep.
There we go.
Why am I making it harder than it needs to be?
On the left there's something.
Yep.
Nailed it.
Wait, that just turns that on.
Okay.
What am I doing here?
You know what?
It's probably time to save the game.
How about we go do that?
Take me down slowly.
This is so good.
I had one job.
Oh, look.
My bubble persists through death.
That's interesting.
Ring up the people.
Let them know we're good.
We're actually really good.
Okay, so we have a fast travel location here now.
And I suspect we can go to the left now down there.
And make some stuff happen.
Now that we have the wand.
I love the wand.
Don't you just love some...
Wanding!
Oh, God.
Wait.
Make it easy.
Not harder.
Bruh.
Okay, I gotta find the sweet spot.
Okay, fine.
Fine.
Be that way.
I can do it myself.
Yeah, so something was going on down here.
Let's slowly descend and have a look.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Sweet!
I don't know what I did, but...
Something I did.
I don't know what I did.
Maybe I unlocked this path right here?
Oh, I thought I could stand on it!
No!
What the fuck, man?
Seriously?
Wait, how do I get back in there now?
Eh?
Oh, I see the lever up there.
I see, I see.
I see your stance.
The B1 is great!
Oh, shit.
Dude, imagine all the new places we can get to with this.
Oh, my God.
I'm already seeing one place.
In my mind.
Oh, my God.
I'm...
Please, focus!
Dude.
I'm losing my mind.
Ha!
Fucking bubble breaking is driving me nuts.
There we go.
Did it.
Okay, now.
Slowly down.
And let's remember, we can't stand on it.
Come on.
God, the atmosphere here is incredible.
Feels like the sewers, in a way.
Wait a sec.
I didn't flip the switch.
I forgot about that.
Completely.
Ha ha!
Let's try that again, eh?
I was...
I was taken by the atmosphere and the environments.
I was looking at...
No!
Emergency bubble generation!
Oh, that works, I guess.
Wait.
I'm not fast enough!
Come on.
Boom!
Yeah!
There we go.
Sweet!
I'm so good.
And...
Boo!
We made it.
Now.
Don't try to jump on that pillar like a dumbass again.
It's not gonna work.
What?
Okay.
I fell for that one, alright?
I fell for it.
That's really funny, actually.
And...
Go!
Made it.
Time to bwant.
Love the bwant.
So, okay.
Let me think.
So when I do that...
I guess I bubble straight up.
Yeah.
I bubble straight up.
Okay.
Straight up bubbling.
Let me just practice.
Okay.
You ready?
Yeah!
We got a Paraguay!
Is it gonna spit seats at me or something?
I have a feeling...
Something's gonna go wrong here.
Fuck you.
Oh!
Uh.
Okay.
Prediction.
I'm gonna hit it with this to make it flab its wings.
Produce a wind current.
I'm gonna use that with my bubbles.
To reach someplace crazy.
There it is.
That's the prediction.
Uh...
But I guess I just jump down?
Maybe I jump to you?
Uh.
Huh?
Oh!
Oh, you little...
Bitch!
Wow!
How fast are you?
Oh, you're very fast.
Well...
What are you gonna do about my, uh...
My little disc here?
Wait, what?
Okay, okay, okay.
We're safe.
Nerd!
Okay, good enough.
Haha!
Outsmarted.
Outplayed.
And now we ring up the people.
And let them know how we outsmarted the bird.
Full on health?
Health?
Why did I say it like that?
This one is blocked.
That means we gotta find a button.
Somewhere.
Oh!
What is this place even?
Those look like ghosts.
Actually, goats!
Don't they look like goats?
Look at the horns!
And the nose!
That's so goat!
So it's kinda like a goat ghost.
A goat...
I...
You know what I mean.
We got buttons?
Actually, there was a path to the left.
Oh!
Let me play you the song of my people?
He's not impressed.
What about a...
What is it with...
Okay, so these sharks in the...
In the tubes...
Has got to mean something.
You like bubbles?
Oh!
Oh ho ho ho ho!
What?
That's awesome!
Alright!
Well, shit, I don't want to go here, though.
Uh...
Take me back?
Please?
Can I...
Can I go back?
Oh god, do I have to do this again?
Fine.
Oh man.
Okay, well...
Now we know what all those shark heads mean.
That's really cool.
You know what I love about this game?
You try something, you're like...
Nah, probably not.
I mean, that was mostly just RNG, I guess.
Me trying that, but...
Man, the feeling of discovery is...
Incredible.
I feel smart, you know?
That's a great feeling.
Better than feeling dumb.
That's for sure.
Oh!
No!
I wasn't ready!
I...
I wasn't ready.
I threw it, and then I had to...
React, you know?
Instead of...
Doing it proactively, like you should.
This game is surprisingly difficult.
The platforming is crazy difficult.
Hopla!
I just noticed that I do a spin every time I jump.
That's neat.
Made it.
Okay.
But wait a minute, what about...
There's something going on to the left?
Maybe.
Wait, if I flick that switch...
What then?
Then the bottom ones turn on?
Oh!
Oh my god, I see!
We're gonna cage him in!
Oh, that's smart.
There's multiple ways to do this.
I like my way.
It's faster.
This is for the noobs.
Wait!
Wait, I saved here, but why didn't I get...
Oh, because I did this.
Okay, so now that we know that...
Maybe I put a shark here?
I want to make an in and an out.
Dude, we're gonna mark this.
Are you ready?
Check it out.
We're gonna have a mark for out and in.
I think this is gonna be in.
This is gonna be out.
In.
And then...
Oh shit, where did we emerge?
Here.
Out, and then we're gonna do this.
Watch.
Oh, no, no, no, don't, don't, don't, don't.
No, no, no, no.
Huh?
Tell me that isn't genius.
Look at this.
We're gonna map...
All the tubes.
Tube network coming in.
Oh my god, this feels incredible.
I love this game.
This game just...
Dude, the pencil?
One of the best things ever.
How come no more games have this?
This is such a needed thing.
It's all games.
Okay.
Let's take a break here.
This is looking exciting.
I gotta go stretch my legs a little bit.
And also...
Oh, did my phone activate saying some bullshit?
It did.
God damn it.
Sorry if you could hear that.
Anyway, I'll see you guys in five minutes.
Break time.
Alright, we're back.
Man.
Okay.
Get comfortable.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Uh, the cord is annoying.
I really need to find a way to make this controller wireless.
Don't dream about bunnies.
It's time to yo-yo.
Yo-yo the shit.
Whoop.
Nice.
Oi!
What the...
Okay!
Why you have a, uh, arrow on your head?
Let's go...
Oh, look!
Are you gonna hurt me if I...
Are you gonna squish me?
Oh!
He jumps over holes.
What am I supposed to do here?
Do I hide?
Oh, I love destroying things.
That sounds really funny.
But you know what I mean.
It's just so simple, but so well done.
Oh, shit.
Uh-oh.
I have no more thingies.
What do I do?
Run!
Fuck me.
Uh...
Uh!
Done!
What the fuck?
What are you supposed to do?
I couldn't do anything!
Uh...
Back here.
Oh my god.
No.
Back up.
Good.
Okay.
Smooth.
Oh god.
Maybe...
Maybe I can use you.
Emancipator.
Whatever you are.
Isn't that what they're called?
Come here!
Can I...
Oh, maybe I can...
Use you somehow.
Against this guy.
Maybe I push...
Fuck!
Okay.
He can squish you.
It's bad.
He...
He fat boy.
Oh, crap.
Man.
I've died like a hundred times in this game already.
Okay.
Do not get squished.
Oh.
He breaks these too.
Okay.
That's neat.
So.
What is the plan here?
Um...
Oh!
Ah!
I see.
Thank you.
That's what I needed.
Scrap that too.
I'm scared.
So, two to the right.
Oh.
What?
What's happening?
I know what it is.
It's an owl.
Going, cuckoo, cuckoo.
You know, like those clocks?
A cuckoo clock.
Fuck you.
Ha-ha!
Good night, egg.
Good night.
May you sleep well.
I forgot what the next stage of egg was.
Right, chicken.
Of course.
Kidding.
Uh, how many did I need for the next door?
I don't remember.
Was that a...
That's a candle.
We can lit...
We can light that.
Somehow.
Probably from down here.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna play proactive here.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
Slowly descend.
That's right.
Look at that.
Beautiful performance.
Ha-ha.
I love that it destroys things on the way back as well.
Yeah!
Light that ca...
Oh, look at that light.
It's so cozy.
I wanna take a nap here.
Just hang out a bit.
Oh, uh...
Okay.
Ah...
Oh, you're stuck down there now.
I see.
Interesting.
So...
We need another one of you.
Um...
Yeah.
Two more buttons.
What should I call you?
Maybe...
That'll be Sasha.
That's Sasha.
I think that's fitting.
Feels Sasha-like with that headpiece, doesn't it?
Okay.
Um...
We need another Sasha.
Or...
We go up to the left and discover something there.
I think that's a good idea.
There he is.
Okay.
But if I stand here...
Oh!
That worked!
Okay!
I thought I needed another one.
Fuck.
Uh...
Oh, we're doing this again!
Okay.
Awesome.
Shortcut unlocked.
Save the game.
Call the people!
Let them know we're good!
What is...
There's this weird flower here.
What's that?
Can I entice you guys...
With music?
Oh, you're reset now.
You don't care at all, do you?
Alright.
Just checking for more secrets in this room.
I don't see any.
Okay, let's see here.
So we have some levers.
So lever on the right.
The water needs to go in the center.
Gotcha.
We may have to do...
Wait, what?
This way.
Oh!
Wait.
Wait, what just happened?
Do that again.
He's being lifted.
Huh?
That activates a fan.
Oh, I see now.
It's actually not...
It's water, isn't it?
Because it's a whale.
The whale sprouts water up through its ears.
But how does that...
What's this?
Oh, wait, wait.
I see, I see.
Do I need to go...
Here?
I need to wait.
So he's gonna do this now.
Ha!
What?
Wait a minute.
Oh, I gotta make him touch the button on the top right.
I understand now.
I get it.
I see.
Smart.
Very smart.
Fly!
And then...
What did the other button do?
I forgot.
Ah, okay.
There we go.
Look at that teamwork.
Incredible.
Careful there.
Oh my god, it's so funny.
Okay, so here...
We have problems, don't we?
How on earth are we gonna...
Oh, shit.
I see.
I probably should have adjusted these before.
Beforehand, huh?
Maybe that's correct?
That seems about right.
And then we have this guy over here.
I see it now.
I see it.
Oh no, the vines!
Do the vines always...
The vines always break it.
Okay.
So we bring out the disc, I guess.
Oh no, the vines break the disc too!
What's happening here?
Is that a wolf?
Sounds like a wolf.
Howling, you know?
Um...
Oh!
Oh my god, really?
Check this out.
You ready?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
That's great!
Oh man!
Fuckin' hell.
That's incredible, that.
No!
It don't reach!
I guess we...
Oh no, I see what the problem is.
Of course we gotta use the bottom one too.
Obviously.
Oh yeah, right.
You're gonna...
Do that.
Ha ha ha!
Nice.
Hey!
Ah!
There we go.
Good enough!
And then this one...
Almost.
Yeah!
This is great!
Uh...
I forgot how buttons work.
There we go.
Oh wait.
There we go!
Fill her up!
Beautiful.
Wait, what happened?
Oh, the door's opened!
Nice.
He's looking for his secrets.
It sounds like someone's slurping the water.
Uh-oh.
That's a whale!
And it doesn't look friendly.
Wait.
Are you trying to tell me something?
Wait, what?
Okay, so now he resets.
Down.
Down, down, up, down.
Okay.
Motherfucker.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Brother.
Fuck, I missed it.
I gotta start.
I gotta wait.
Wait till he resets.
Okay, that's the reset.
Now.
What do you do?
Wait, was that part of it?
Left, right?
Down.
Down, left, down, down.
Down again.
Again.
And left.
You bastard.
Okay, I don't understand.
I think...
I don't get it.
But I think I gotta get across here.
I guess I can use this, but I...
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
He's happy.
Oh, we got buttons in there.
Okay, okay, okay.
What the?
He ate me?
What the fuck, dude?
Okay, did not see that coming.
I thought he was friendly.
Bastard.
Thought you were on my side.
Unbelievable.
See ya.
Noob.
Okay, okay, okay.
Now, obviously we gotta...
Do something different here.
Shit.
No!
Don't fall down.
Maybe we disc this.
We wait.
Now.
Follow me.
Blow it upwards.
Yes!
Incredible.
Oh, God.
I didn't see that.
That's awesome.
Do I grab the food, though?
That's risky.
Probably not.
Risky food.
Illegal Danish.
I see a path on the right as well, actually.
A little secret.
What was that?
Wait, can I draw with the mouse?
Oh, shit.
That's way better.
Oh, my God.
Dude.
Okay, this is great.
Way better.
Sweet!
Okay, we're doing that from now on.
Anyway, I was going to draw on the map.
That was the whole point.
Here.
Alright, dude.
Come on.
I see spikes!
So we may have to descend with a bubble.
Also.
Let's go down.
I'm scared.
Oh, we got to fill these up with water.
Ah, shit.
I see.
Okay, then.
Yeah, good!
Try again, buddy.
That's not good enough.
Ah!
That's not enough.
Oh, that one's full, I guess.
Yes!
Boom, baby!
Oh, wait.
Oh, shit.
Hold on to that.
Let me see the map.
I see something on the top left.
Hold on.
We're not leaving.
Not yet.
Uh, how did I...
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
Yeah!
Heh!
Can't fool me.
SHIT!
Mother crapper!
I had it.
Unreal, actually.
NOOOOO!
Ah!
Fuck!
It's fine.
Oh my god, wait, where am I now?
I'm set back so much!
It's horrible.
See ya, nerd!
Oh, that's...
These bastards.
Of course you put spikes right there where you intend to jump, huh?
You like that?
Spikes?
Fuck your spikes.
Up, up spike.
Spike them.
Spike it.
Good.
Okay.
Now.
Two hearts.
It's not good.
It's bad, in fact.
I'm gonna die again.
I can tell already.
It's gonna be the end of me.
Focus.
Focus!
Go!
Yes, dude!
Nailed it.
But wait.
I seen some more.
A bigger secret?
Haha!
Wha...
Huh?
How'd I die?
I didn't see what happened!
What happened?
Fuck!
I didn't see what happened.
Oh my god.
Off we go.
Yoink!
Didn't fall for the spikes that time.
Yeah!
Look at that.
Beautiful.
First try.
It's gonna be easy.
Wait.
Wait for it.
And now!
Oh my god.
Beautiful.
Oh!
There's spikes!
Wait.
That's a problem.
Unless...
Can I just destroy them?
I can't!
It's the undestroyable variety.
But I do sense...
Something up here.
This...
Yeah.
For sure.
Do I hear a cat?
Shit!
Oh my god.
What the...
Dude, you can't do this?
Huh?
Oh my god.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Oh, that's fast.
That's a...
Wait.
How do I retrieve it?
I messed it up.
I messed it up again.
I'm too slow with it.
So maybe I do it when...
There.
Okay.
And...
Uh...
Wait.
Need to calculate.
Okay.
I have an idea.
Oh, that's way better.
Oh, way better!
We can't be hitting those up there now.
We... let... let be careful.
Can I... oh, I can't shoot this while I'm on it!
Uh...
Ah, shit.
What?
I thought they would destroy the spikes!
No!
I'm making bad mistakes now.
It's all over.
Oh my god.
I'm just horrible.
There we go.
Careful now.
Slowly.
Ah!
Close one.
Okay, so we have two lives.
Ah, that was a bit too slow.
Wait, what is my plan even when I get up there?
That was a bit too slow again.
Too slow.
Dude, this is like...
really difficult.
Okay, yeah, so you die from that, but...
Maybe the destruction persists up there.
You know, if you can get up there and destroy it, then you get back down.
That should work.
That was too slow.
What?
And...
Uh... wait.
How the fuck...
are you supposed to do this?
Can I...
really not bubble here, or...
Bro!
This game is hard as hell, man!
Aw...
What the fuck?
Are you serious?
I'm almost giving up on this.
Aw, man.
Okay, I'm getting impatient.
This is bad.
Focus.
Why did...
I don't understand why I'm doing wrong there, now.
I used to do that.
Pretty well.
Now I can't do it anymore.
Can I...
blow bubbles while on this?
Hm.
NOOOOI!
Okay, so when I do the last one, I gotta quickly jump off of it.
I see.
That should be doable.
The last one, we jump off quick.
Fuck a duck.
Oh sh...
No!
No, no, no, no.
Dude, I am not leaving without this secret.
Oh, no!
We're fine.
Oh, I'm gonna listen to this beeping now.
Okay, I'm not.
Okay, get ready to jump off.
Can we really not yo-yo here?
Why not?
I can't do anything...
Okay.
Look, we do it and quickly jump off to the right.
Quickly jump off to the right.
What?!
It's not hitting anything!
Let's try that again.
No!
I didn't jump off!
Fuck!
You know what?
Fuck that!
I can't believe that.
We're gonna wait with that.
Let's mark it on the map.
I don't know what's going on, but...
I don't understand.
It seems impossible.
Okay, let's go back here.
I actually forgot what was down here.
Ah shit, I didn't mean to.
God damn it.
Oh, we gotta do this again!
Okay.
I thought it was done forever now.
Good.
Ah, I fucked it up.
No, I didn't.
Wow.
We made it.
Ooh.
Oh, is it...
It's one of the flames!
There's a seahorse in the back.
The flame.
Bubble flame.
Ho ho ho!
Found the bee flame.
Oh, it's not...
Oh.
I thought it was an item.
It's a...
It is something I picked up.
It's on the right side now.
I see.
Okay.
Bee flame.
Oh, look!
It's teaching me!
Oh, okay.
Cool.
Oh, shit.
Wait.
Whoops.
Let's just give it a sec.
Open your mouth!
Okay, there we go.
Yeah, asshole.
Okay.
Yeah!
Take me!
On a trip!
Holy shit, where are we going?
I broke something!
Whoa.
Chest!
Oh my god.
Ha!
I'm back here!
Okay, let's mark it.
In fact, instead of using these symbols, I've changed my mind.
Let's not do this.
Because I want to use these symbols for other things on the map.
We can just draw it.
It's fine.
Uh, no.
Do this.
Then go...
Uh...
Oh, right.
We're gonna do like, uh...
Circle and...
X.
That's the new plan.
So over here...
Down here...
We're gonna have a...
By the way, there's something here.
Something there.
Anyway.
Circle.
That takes us to where we are now.
X.
Ha ha ha!
Ah, that's not very pretty, is it?
That's better.
Beautiful!
Absolutely beautiful!
Now, these circles may confuse me, actually.
Maybe I do...
Triangle.
For the input.
I like that.
Triangle is input.
X is output.
Boom.
How you like them?
Apples.
Question is, I can't...
Get back up, right?
Fuck!
I wanna solve these puzzles down here!
But you know what?
Maybe we'll find an item that will make that way easier.
I'm also just now noticing...
What the hell is this down here?
That looks like a turtle!
Oh!
Ah!
It's the hub!
Oh my god.
Incredible.
Eat these.
Okay, okay.
Wait, that...
Yeah, that's an X.
That's good.
Now we save the game.
Save that game.
Oh man, okay.
Uh...
How about we check out the egg room?
We got a couple eggs.
Maybe something happens.
Egg room.
Excuse me?
Nothing happens, eh?
So that one is...
32.
Wow, so it's...
Exponential increase.
Does that say games?
Or am I imagining things?
Read it.
Squint your eyes and read that.
Tell me it doesn't say games.
Maybe.
Maybe not, actually.
Okay, so there's stuff up here still that we didn't get to.
Let go that way.
It looks like I've already been up here, kinda.
Oh, look at all these weird paths we haven't taken.
There's also a question mark there.
Let's try going that way.
I like...
Let's mark the map a little bit here.
Like this...
Seems interesting.
Uh, let's make it a bit bigger.
Here.
I don't wanna block things.
Um...
Let me see here.
Something here for sure.
Something there.
Here maybe.
Here for sure.
This area is big.
I love this ability to draw on the map.
It's so...
Simple.
Good.
Fantastic job.
By the developers on that.
So how do I get up there now?
The long path?
Or do we have a little shortcutty?
I think I see a shortcutty.
In fact, I'm kinda considering playing this game with keyboard and mouse...
Like completely now.
I wonder how that's gonna be.
W, A, S, D.
Jump.
And how do I...
Oh, that's E?
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Ah, okay.
Ah, maybe later.
For now I'm gonna stick to the controller.
And now we gotta go up.
Also, remember...
Wasn't there a switch here?
Something was happening underneath this waterfall.
Or am I confusing this with another region?
I may be confusing it.
I think I'm thinking of this region there.
Okay.
Let's go up here.
Thank you.
Doggo!
Crap!
That's for you, buddy!
Right!
I remember this.
But did I go over here?
I mean, I must have.
Look at the map.
Let's just go back up here.
Oh, that was easy.
I had so much trouble with that last time.
Oh, I'm full.
Okay.
Eat.
Why is...
Isn't that...
That's like a dog penguin.
Look!
I mean, dog, uh...
Dolphin.
Uh-oh.
I remember the slinky being a thing here.
Good.
Uh, what did the other button do, though?
Let's...
Oh!
Oh, brother!
Whoa!
Huh?
Oh, shit!
Here we go.
Whoa.
Oh, this looks neat.
There's a camel.
Nice.
Eat that.
But what is this place?
Shortcut?
Oh, shit!
That's how we get here.
Okay, cool.
I didn't mean to fall all the way down.
Fuck.
So I guess we unlock the shortcut.
That's neat.
But I want more.
I'm not done.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
What did this lever do?
Right.
And then we got the chest.
And we were done with that, right?
Maybe that lever changed something over here.
I thought maybe they were going up now.
But you can probably change it somehow to go up.
I can see that being a thing.
How about shit?
How do I...
Ah, just back down, I guess.
All the way down.
I really enjoy the backgrounds on these maps.
You know, the stuff you can't walk on.
There's a lot of detail in it.
Surprisingly.
Such a simple game, graphically, I mean.
This is almost like a desert.
We got palm trees.
And cacti.
That's good.
Good boy.
You wanna play a bit more?
Okay.
You can't jump for it?
Now what did I do wrong last time?
I did something here and then I...
And then something happened.
Maybe I fell down.
Save.
Okay, so there's a button up there.
Oh yeah.
I remember now.
I can also go down.
Oh, it's down here.
Ooh!
Found a match!
What is that?
Oh, is that the...
That's what's gonna blow.
Okay, we have a fast travel tube here.
Time to map it.
So where am I now?
Let's mark it.
No, no.
It was a triangle, right?
Triangle.
Okay.
Take me.
Where are we going, buddy?
This is very rain world-y right now.
I feel like a slug cat.
Oh no!
I saw a chest!
Did I just flip a switch?
What just happened?
Oh!
That takes me here, huh?
Well, well, well.
Now where did I come from?
Triangle, triangle...
Oh, was it all the way up here?
Holy shit.
I don't want to be here now!
Take me back!
Oh, but wait a sec.
There's gotta be a candle in here.
Candle me.
I do remember taking that chest up there, but...
I really can't enter the map, huh?
Oh no, it's this spot.
Right.
Am I seeing secrets while I'm here?
I see something there.
Maybe that's important?
Just make a line there.
Actually, I don't know.
Maybe...
I like the arrow.
That's sure to draw attention.
Shit.
Oh no, this is not the way.
The right side, I do remember this part.
There we go.
Okay, so wait...
Surely I can open your mouth.
Oh!
I understand how it works now, guys.
You have to stand in the spot where the eye lights up.
Oh, okay.
Very cool.
I was so confused last time because it worked on the bear and then it didn't work on...
Well, I don't know what you are.
What are you even?
You're like a...
I don't know.
Like an iguana?
Maybe?
Okay.
I see a spot on the right, actually.
We can investigate that.
Oh, wait.
Uh...
Oh, dude!
All the places we can go with the bubble now!
We can practically go anywhere!
That is crazy.
Wait, that died over there?
We could also perhaps remove this now.
Uh...
Remove that.
Save the game.
But there's something on the other side of this wall here.
Let's make this go the other way again.
And try going downstairs.
Because this is the spot I thought of immediately when I got the bubble.
That's right!
Turn around!
Okay.
Look at that!
There's a fish on the right!
Fast travel.
Uh...
But getting to that is pretty much impossible.
Unless you're really fast...
If I jump down now...
There's no way you make it.
There is no way you make that.
Unless...
Check this out.
What?!
It broke?!
I didn't do anything!
It just broke on its own!
Wait, what's hap- It- It got blown to the right?
Or...
What?!
Okay, yeah, you- You can't do this.
Can I go below that?
No, okay.
Okay.
Huh.
Oh my god, this is so much easier.
What was the point of being up here?
Do we try to map these now, or...
Later?
Because I feel like if I do it now, I'm gonna end up on the other side of the map.
Let's wait.
How about shit?
We can't even...
Oh, shit!
Oh, we got cats in...
Cages!
Let's mark it immediately, before we forget.
Oh, that's an easy path.
There we go.
Aw!
I-I-I'm gonna rescue you, don't worry.
I love animals.
This door is inaccessible, it seems.
Oh my god, this looks complicated.
Hold on, I gotta blow my nose.
Hey, buddies.
What do you think about this?
You like yo-yos?
Yo-yo!
Aw, I know!
I'm coming!
I'm gonna-I'm gonna...
rescue you somehow.
Uh, let's just use this, huh?
Wait, I see a secret!
Bottom right, secret.
You could definitely make these go the other way.
Somehow.
That's going down!
What?
Yes!
Uh, that opened one of them?
We gotta press a couple more.
Okay, the fact that these are going in here means I can go in here, right?
Oh no, I guess I can't.
Okay.
Oh, how am I gonna...
Can I make you turn around here, or...?
Maybe music will entice.
Maybe I entice the animals.
And they send a mating call out, and everyone else knows?
Oh shit!
Wait, something's going on!
Wait, could it be...
Could it be that?
Uh...
There, there, there, there.
Bup.
Bup, bup, bup, bup, bup.
Wait, what?
There.
There, there.
Oh, right, okay.
Wait.
Nope.
Yay!
Fuck yeah!
That did it!
Oh, okay!
That's one of them!
We gotta find more melodies!
Oh my god.
Fuck yeah, dude!
Sick!
Okay, I don't know why I'm...
This is bad, isn't it?
I'm gonna die!
Ah, I couldn't think fast enough.
Fuck.
Save the game, I guess.
Ah, but now it's going up again.
Maybe I do wanna go up again?
Let me think.
What was up there?
Was there anything that looked like a puzzle?
Maybe...
Actually...
Wait.
So we got the melody from here.
Right over there, right?
There's probably one on the other side as well.
And it looks like I can possibly access it from...
Here?
Or there.
Right?
That's what it looks like to me.
Um...
I...
Let me try and reverse this again.
There you go.
Now it's reversed.
Let's take this pipe!
Oh, we can't take it though!
Yeah, this needs to be reversed.
Basically, we need to find another animal in a cage and have them run the other way.
Yeah.
Wait a minute, I wonder...
Is that gonna push me?
Oh, I thought he could push me on the bubble.
Okay.
Too bad.
There's also this symbol on the right.
Take me back here.
Okay.
I know, I'm coming for you.
I just need to find out the melodies.
Uh...
So if...
If I jump down here...
Let me plan this a little bit.
I have three HP.
I can jump straight down and that will maybe work.
I hit that button.
Okay, cool.
What then?
Oh!
We got an animal down there!
Can I make you...
Run the other way from here?
Oh, I didn't mean to jump down.
Didn't even fucking see you there.
This one seems impossible on the left.
Wait, how does that even work?
How would I do that?
I jump down over here.
I hit the spikes.
Are those the spikes I can destroy?
I can't tell.
Uh...
Sh...
Oh shit!
Oh no, oh no!
I'm scared.
Oh, I made it!
Sweet!
Now what?
Okay, I can't destroy it, but...
Oh!
Check it out.
Joy!
Yes, dude!
Uh, can I jump high enough though?
No, I can't!
Where...
Where's my buddy?
I can't see my character!
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
I found it.
Uh, so now I guess I gotta go...
Like this maybe?
And then...
I'm dead!
Oh, fuck!
Ahhhh!
Shit!
I hate being squished!
It's the worst fate ever!
I hate seeing it come and not being able to do anything about it.
Wait, what is making you turn?
Is it just the...
That's not making you turn.
So, it's not hitting you specifically.
Really?
It's...
If you see the green light...
Then you turn.
Weird.
Okay.
I think I gotta do that down there.
Uh, bubbles.
T'ah!
At least you don't lose HP when you fall in the water.
I'm very grateful for that.
Eat it!
Take me on a trip!
Okay.
Let's try this again, eh?
So why are you not reacting to my...
Yo-yo, huh?
We're gonna go...
Oh, wait.
Come on, react to it!
Bastard!
I gotta do the other side, I think?
Oh, god.
Okay.
Yo-yo, yo-yo!
Yes!
Oh, shit!
Oh, here we go, here we go!
Oh, wait.
How?
Here?
Yes!
Uhhh...
I... I don't know.
I don't know what to do!
Where do I go, where do I go?
Okay, I guess I can stay like this for a bit.
Umm...
If I jump down to the left, I'm gonna die.
Huh.
This seems impossible.
Oh no, of course not!
I see.
I understand.
We can-we can do this through the floor!
Uh, can you please let me have that back?
Thank you.
Yes!
Oh shit!
No!
Oh no!
God damn it!
That is the hardest puzzle in this game!
It's such a long path as well to get back here.
Suck it up!
Oh!
There we go.
Jump!
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
Let's- let's actually do this, huh?
So we got the two buttons.
Which opened this up here.
There we go.
That's two out of three.
So I'm assuming this room is done.
Let's see.
Does it look like there's a...
hidden path or something?
I don't think so.
That room is done, Cease!
Eat that fruit.
Okay.
Now, this path...
I see the button up there, but...
Alright, let's see if we can't find a way.
So, we gotta change the direction of these.
And I think there's gotta be a rotating animal somewhere here.
The question is, where is it?
Just gotta throw our yo-yo around and hope for the best.
Not there.
Oh, I can't even get back down.
Oh, wait!
Everything is affected by the guy on the right, no?
Like, the whole mechanism...
I actually can't tell yet.
Let's see.
Fuck!
I thought I was right.
Huh.
Wait, did it reset?
What?
I'm so confused.
Why didn't that do anything?
Oh!
Cuckoo!
Why are we cuckooing?
Oh!
It changed the direction of the bottom one!
I was looking at the left one.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Aha!
Look at this.
Eat it.
Takes me here.
Oh!
But they're reversed now!
Okay, sick.
Let me note that down.
So, where was I exactly here?
Let's see.
So I went...
Uh...
I went here.
Went there.
Then I went to this one.
So it's actually there.
Which takes me...
There.
Okay.
Let's go!
It's so satisfying solving these.
It's difficult, but it's satisfying.
It's really...
Oh!
Here.
It's really nice.
Oh, yeah.
Bubble time!
Chest!
I saw it.
Another chest.
Okay.
Noted.
And we came from...
Here.
That's a horrible triangle.
Blow shit up!
Oh!
That's so satisfying!
Yeah!
Ooh!
Look at that shortcut though!
Oh my goodness!
Love it!
Hoho!
Food!
I don't need it.
Uh...
Yeah, take the bubble!
Going on a trip!
And now I'm back here.
Oh, I see!
That's so good.
Okay.
So where did we end up?
Here, right?
Oops.
Triangle.
X.
There we go.
Cool!
Alrighty!
But that doesn't really help us with rescuing the other cats.
But I guess we need melodies for that.
Is there anything else I want to be doing down here?
There is one thing I want to do.
There's still a button that we have to get to.
Let's try and get to it.
So, wait.
Am I kind of...
Stunlocked here now?
How do I...
Proceed?
Like, I...
I can't go left anymore.
I can't go up either.
Oh!
It just occurred to me.
So check out the symbol on...
These.
The cat symbol on these, right?
And the cat symbol on the bottom one.
It's different.
So, of course, one animal is responsible for the up-down.
The other one is for the left-right.
Gotcha.
That makes sense.
Makes a lot of sense.
Now, how do I proceed?
I guess I just go back here.
Bubble.
Hopsa!
Okay!
Sweet, sweet, sweet.
Then, we're gonna go...
I think I want to go up here now.
Maybe check out that arrow there.
That seems good.
In the center of the screen.
So, to get there, we would have to...
God, what is that?
Wait a second.
Why is this part of the map not being revealed?
There's definitely something here.
I've been here for sure.
Have I not?
I feel like this is very reminiscent.
But okay.
To get there...
Is there a path through here?
Wait.
No!
I...
Didn't mean to jump in his mouth!
Fuck!
God, okay.
You know what?
We're gonna play the song of someone else's people.
I fucked it up.
Brown.
Okay, we made it.
Now, let's see.
Let's see here.
Um...
Re...
Oh, I think I know what to do with the recess.
We gotta find the...
The other disc.
The...
Where was that?
It was close to...
Oh, God.
This map is very hard to read.
I don't remember where I found the disc.
It's not down here.
There.
Why did I put a B there?
B for what?
I don't know why I did that.
Why...
Why did I do that?
Something else I need to do.
I need to mark, um...
The exit and...
Entrance points of these fast travel ones.
So I think I'm gonna do this...
Bear.
And then we're gonna find out where the bear is.
By jumping through it.
Wait, that's not a bear.
That's...
Yeah, that's a bear.
And I'm here now.
So maybe I'll...
Maybe I'll do...
Yeah, just write.
Bear.
Shit, I can't write.
Bear!
Good enough for me.
Whoops!
Maybe we proceed from here.
Oh god, this map is very big.
It's huge.
I guess I go up through here.
To go up there.
Yeah.
We walk past here.
Oh, but Brian is in the way.
Oh...
Oh, we can't even get through here!
That's not a path!
We gotta go right.
Um...
Gonna wake him up.
There we go.
Back through here.
These almost look like, uh...
Easter eggs, don't they?
Actually, that's...
Exactly what this looks like.
Easter eggs.
They're all colorful.
Maybe...
That's the point, you know?
Because the game has full...
Has so many Easter eggs or secrets.
We have a lynx on the left.
A hologram of it.
Can I get there?
In a smart way?
Ah!
Oh shit!
Oh ho!
Wait, where am I going?
Um...
Oh!
This is where I want it to be!
Ha ha ha!
Perfect!
Uh...
Actually, let's just make...
That's horrible.
That's a skull, okay?
It's a horrible skull.
But you know what I mean.
Okay, so recess...
Is down there.
How am I gonna...
Do that.
Okay, so I go through here.
So...
We...
We snatch.
We go right.
Down, down, down, down, down.
Past the phone.
Down left.
Down right.
Oh god.
There's no way I'll remember that.
Okay, here we go.
Fuck you!
See ya, buddy!
You suck!
Oh, god.
Oh!
Whoops!
I messed up there.
Down, down, down, down, down!
Fast, fast, fast.
Down.
I think.
Yes!
Down!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's fast.
Oh shit.
We're done.
Is this the one?
It is!
Bubbles!
No!
Oh no!
I didn't have the item out!
Gee!
Alright.
Ring around the Rosie.
Hey buddy, come here.
Oh god.
I have an idea.
Oh fuck.
Gah!
Okay, we can make it.
We can make it.
Just run, run, run, run, and then bubble.
Bubble time.
Fuck!
I can't do it with the pressure!
It's impossible.
It's impossible!
Oh my god.
It's doable.
That!
Insert!
Oh fuck you, I can't do it!
Oh my...
Come on!
Bro!
I guess that's not what I'm supposed to do.
Well, what the hell then?
Okay, I don't know.
Let me play you the song of someone else's people.
Okay.
Um...
I wonder if I can, um...
Can I open your eyes?
Somewhere else?
Maybe here?
Open your eyes.
No?
Oh!
Wha- Oh, oh!
Oh,
no shit!
We're back here.
Huh!
And look!
Five candles are lit.
I was right.
Well shit, um...
I don't wanna go there.
There.
So what is this?
That's a...
Evil fish?
I guess?
Let's just call it, uh...
Fush.
Cause it's evil.
It's like a little corrupted, you know?
No, that's...
That's horrible.
Also, that's...
Is that the bottom one I'm at?
Yeah.
Fush.
Okay.
So now I'm here.
What about the recess, though?
Wait a minute.
Doesn't this kinda look like a cat?
I...
I'm so convinced we gotta bring that disc somewhere.
The question is where?
Like, it would be the perfect puzzle, right?
To run from that thing with the disc and bring it somewhere.
Okay, what if...
Oh!
I know how to get there now!
I know how to get there, dude!
We...
Oh, this is sick.
The spot we have never been able to get to, we can now get to.
Cause of our newfound powers.
Let's go!
Oh!
Oh, but wait.
No!
Oh, it breaks on the vines.
Don't it?
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
I can't do it.
Fuck!
Oh, man!
Fine.
The firecrack.
Maybe I can scare you into submission.
And you'll come down to me.
You don't care at all, do you?
I think I need to access it from the left, so...
I would have to come in from...
here.
So we gotta go to bubble region.
Which is actually right next to us.
Yeah, let's go back there.
Oh, shit.
And of course we gotta go...
Oh!
Let me see here.
That is the cat!
Wait.
Oh, the eyes turn on!
Look!
The eyes are turning on when I get close.
Green.
Pink.
Red.
And...
Aqua.
My mama said.
Wait, what?
Your eyes are glowing.
Anyway, let's go to the bubble region and investigate the area.
Keep going left.
Is there a better way?
No.
Yeah, okay, so we gotta get past these bastards!
Uh, here.
Down and right.
Oh yeah, here we go, buddy.
This is it.
There was nothing else up top.
No?
Okay.
Down we go!
Stack up the bubbles!
What?
Huh?
I just took damage for some reason.
See ya later, nerds!
Actually, wait a minute.
There's something on the left too.
But I think I already investigated that.
But I forgot what I...
found.
Let's take another look.
Oh!
Nice!
A normal egg!
Oh!
I...
I immediately went into the drink.
Oh!
It was the one above I found last time!
Never mind.
Sick!
Finding all the eggs.
Backtracking people?
It always pays off.
Are you gonna hurt me?
Hey!
Better stay above you.
Shit!
Okay.
That's challenging.
Regular intervals?
One, two, three.
Aw, shit.
You can't do it too close to the ceiling, obviously.
But I know what to do.
Whoops.
That was a bit too delayed.
Oh, shit!
Oh, nice!
I can stand on those!
No!
Oh, god.
Hehehehe.
Haha, this is great!
Don't hurt me!
Oh, god.
Wait, does it last?
Oh!
Oh, it lasts forever.
Okay.
Oh, god.
Ah!
Oh!
Yes!
A great egg!
Oh!
Extra HP!
Very cool!
But, of course, I see the secret already.
Think you can fool me?
The great secret finder 4000?
I think not.
Hehehehe.
Oh, shit.
How am I...
Oh, I see.
I see.
I put it left!
Liar!
The game is lying to me.
I made it left, not right.
The hell?
Oh!
Oops, oops.
Okay.
Don't get impatient now.
Don't get impatient.
Look at that top right one trying to fool me there.
Unbelievable.
Easy.
YOOOOO!
We found it!
It's gone.
Hello?
What just happened?
Wait, I somehow ate it anyway?
Even though I'm full.
How did that happen?
Okay, well, nice!
Found that!
Did that!
Okay, um...
How many eggs do we have now?
23.
Okay.
So, what is it with these eyes lighting up?
Look!
Maybe they need a specific tone each.
Wait.
What was that?
OH!
We gotta put the...
flames inside of here.
On each of them.
I see.
Okay.
These are the great animals of the region.
And their fire has gone out.
We need to...
re... non-extinguish it.
Or light it.
Another word for that.
That's what needs to happen.
And you know what?
These animals are evil right now!
We are turning them good again.
By giving them the flame of ambition.
We have to embolden them.
That's it!
That's what's happening here.
The lands have been corrupted by evil.
And the once great animals of this region...
have fallen.
And their darkest versions of themselves are showing.
We need to suppress that and bring out the light.
Literally.
Boom!
That's it.
Okay, so there's lights up here.
I mean, they look like I can just go grab them.
Maybe we just go grab them?
Also, I did put arrows here.
So, how about we investigate that as well?
Do I hear a frog?
Oh no, that's a quacky.
A duck!
That's a duck right there.
Wait, wait!
He's doing a thing!
Do it again.
Come on.
Make a song.
Quack left.
Quack right.
Okay, buddy.
Sure.
Now, what's going on with this board?
This is obviously a puzzle.
There's stars in the background.
Or what looks like stars.
There's three lines on the left.
You know what?
We're gonna take a picture of this.
Like that.
We're gonna put it in here.
Make it a bit smaller.
Just so we have it.
I have a feeling this may change as we play the game.
Somehow, maybe the colors of the cat will change.
Or the shape of it.
I mean, this is basically pixels.
Right?
Wait.
Could it be...
I was thinking...
Maybe the borders of this board...
Correspond to the borders of the giant map.
And...
Where the X's are, or the stars...
Correspond to an actual position on this map.
Imagine that.
Because I'm thinking in pixels now.
And maybe every pixel is like a little sub-region in the game.
Maybe this represents the map of this game.
I don't know.
Also, something's going on here.
There's two...
Mice...
In holy matrimony.
So I had a question mark there.
Wait.
You know what?
Let's go back there.
Let's see if it was a skill issue.
Or maybe...
Let's just see what's going on.
Wait.
Did I see it?
Oh yeah.
Right.
Oh!
That's water!
Oh shit.
That's not the way then.
This way.
Oh sh- Oh!
Oh!
I forgot about this.
That should...
No wait.
That doesn't take me...
Oh yeah.
It does.
Oh no.
Not this again.
Alright.
We're gonna do it one more time.
I'm pro at it now though.
This is super easy.
Easiest game of my life.
Fuck.
Whoa!
That was close.
Nice.
Good.
There we go.
Look, I ate it anyway.
I forced it in my mouth.
So check out the arrows in the bottom right.
You can barely see them, right?
This lights them up.
So I was wondering...
Maybe the other side...
Also has arrows.
I can't see them from here, but maybe...
No, it doesn't look like it.
It's too dark to see the darn map.
Gotcha.
Okay.
Let's do this part.
This part I'm pretty good at now.
Flip that switch.
Go back.
Oh, wait.
What a nice little puzzle, eh?
Okay, here it comes, here it comes.
The bubbles here are gonna be a little...
No.
Okay, we gotta do this.
Is this actually for real?
It even looks like...
Oh, there's a chest.
Okay, there's a chest.
How do I even get past you?
Like...
Do I jump on this at the right time?
Shit.
There's no way!
I'm too fat!
You can't fit?
Am I crazy?
Like, it's impossible.
Wait, why am I here now, of all places?
Don't tell me I have to do all of this again just to get the chance to do it again.
There's no way, right?
Oh, I should have flipped the switch before I died.
Aw, shit.
Oh my god.
Um...
Is this the best way back?
Oh no, man.
How do I even get back?
I have no clue.
Uh...
In fact, it looks like something is missing up.
Whoops.
It means do that.
Up here.
Like, what is this?
That can't be it.
Destroy these.
Yep!
There we go.
There's no way this is just a food item up here.
Oh!
Oh, look!
We got arrows!
I was looking for hidden paths!
Didn't even look there!
Look at that!
Okay.
So, what is that?
That's, uh...
Right...
Up, right, up.
Okay.
Uh...
Let's do that.
So...
Right...
Oops.
Up, right...
Uh...
Up.
That's down.
And then it was...
Up, left, down.
Like that.
Let's see.
Right, up, right.
Up!
Up, left, down.
Up, up, left, down.
Yeah.
We got it.
Okay.
Alrighty!
Well, uh...
I was about to say, there's no way that there's nothing there, right?
Okay.
So, we found that.
That's kinda huge.
Let's go back to, um...
To the cats.
There we go.
I know the path now.
Jump.
Oh, jump!
Oh!
I didn't have the right thing equipped!
Ugh!
I hate that.
Okay.
We're good now.
Eat it!
Sock me in!
Take me on a trip.
Okay.
So, here we go.
Um...
Let's see.
I'm just gonna do it like this.
Um...
Right.
There.
Here.
Ha-ha!
You're free!
Let's go, little kitty cat!
Nice!
One more!
Hold on, maybe there's one right here.
Let's keep an eye out.
Hold on.
What if I missed...
Dude!
These things are so hard to, uh...
See!
I could easily have missed one.
Uh, one thing I did want to try, though.
Was, what about that button up top?
Like, there's got to be a way to reverse this.
Down here somewhere, right?
Actually, there is this spot here.
Like, what's that all about?
That looks like it's close to this area, so...
Maybe it's important.
There's also a treasure chest here.
That I never got, I guess, since I marked it.
And...
Actually, there's a lot in this region we didn't get, it seems.
Wait.
I wanna go back up.
I guess I can do that from down here.
Ah, but it's not reversed.
Shit.
We gotta go up here first.
There we go.
They're so cute.
The noises they make.
Okay.
Look out for symbols on the walls now.
Now we go back.
Oh wait, I can't go up again!
Uh, yes I can, actually.
We have a pipe.
Bubble time.
Okay.
We make it out.
So...
Now I wanna head up here.
No, uh, over here.
This whole region is ripe with secrets.
So, to get there...
I guess we...
How did we get there?
I guess from down here, actually.
It's right here.
This looks doable.
This background right here...
Makes me think there's a puzzle.
Just the way these lights are positioned, you know?
Okay, so we're back here now.
Wait, what?
Oh!
I didn't see that guy.
Wait, didn't I...
Oh, I got this chest already!
Why did I not remove that from the...
That's a mistake.
There we go.
Gone.
So this region we did...
But...
Oh, this is the dark area!
Oh!
I see.
It just doesn't show up on the map.
That's just a little bit annoying, actually.
Makes me think...
This is also a place I've already been, of course.
Yeah, obviously it is.
But I can't see it, because it's dark.
So we should actually make a little...
Uh...
Simple here.
There's a region there.
There's a region there, too.
Don't get it twisted now!
Um...
Right.
So we gotta go up again.
The question is...
Was there anything else here?
It looks like there may be something here...
But that's not a certain thing.
Maybe someone leads up here?
Let's find out.
Right.
So now I'm here.
I gotta go down.
I do remember this spot!
But that's not what I was looking for.
Can I get down here somehow, without...
Having this guy being annoying?
I don't react to any sounds.
What about a slinky on your head?
Haha!
That actually works.
And now the slinky fells.
Okay, I don't know about that.
I also put a skull here.
I think that's simple for animal.
The evil version.
Let's just try and get some of these flames, huh?
The best way to do that is to go back to the egg room.
Uh...
So I think it may be best to just...
Fast travel?
Yeah.
Now where do we go?
Oh, there's also the bear!
That's here.
Oh, we're actually kinda close to this flame!
Let's check that out.
That's right, that was the whole, uh...
Oh...
Save the game.
Very important.
By the way, am I thinking on, um...
The last cat down here?
Notice the colors of the regions.
We found the two combos down here.
Surely the third is down there as well.
Actually, there's a flame right down there.
Holy shit.
Oh, that's probably, uh...
You can get that when you rescue the cats.
Yeah, that's probably what's gonna happen.
Actually, wait a minute.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep.
I'm right.
I'm right with that.
Now, these two symbols I'm not happy with.
I may remove them.
Actually...
Let's, uh...
Mark where we found the first code.
The first code was found...
Here.
The second code was found...
Um...
Hold on.
I do remember where it was, but I just need to see it.
With my own eyes.
Wait, was it down here?
Oh my god, I can't.
Uh...
There's a big, and then right.
Big, right.
Oh, here, here, here.
Oh, it was actually right there!
I was right next to it!
Oh my god.
Maybe the last one is within that little area.
That can't be, uh...
Coincidence.
One was here.
There was nothing there.
Let's just remember that.
I'll come back.
Now, here.
Okay, so...
We haven't been there yet.
Okay.
Why did I just take damage?
Oh!
The evil bastards in the air!
I see.
Of course.
I almost forgot about those.
I think I needed fireworks against these.
This was very early game.
Right.
Oh!
Could it be?
Oh, I'm too slow!
Fuck!
It's left.
Left.
Dude.
They need to be turned on at the same time.
Oh, sh...
How do I make it actually...
It's so inconsistent.
Like...
Now it works.
I have to stand in a very precise spot.
Yes!
Haha!
We got it!
That's awesome!
Okay.
Sweet.
Is that the elevator?
From earlier that we were on.
I think that may be a different one.
There's a prairie dog on that one!
I wonder if that means anything.
Do I go up?
I think I could.
Oh, the...
No, the vines.
Shit.
Oooh!
It's right there!
The flame is right there!
Wait, what?
Ah!
Okay.
I see a telephone.
And I see buttons!
Nice.
Yeah, I figured.
Okay, so we gotta...
Hit them all in quick succession.
Boom!
No problem.
Ring up the people!
Let them know how successful we have been.
And we have, um...
Timon's on each side.
Look!
I don't know what the name of that animal is, but it's like the one from Timon and Pumbaa.
Right, Timon and...
Is that the same in English?
In Danish it's Timon and Pumbaa.
But maybe it's not the same in English.
I see button.
But for that...
Okay, okay.
An elevator or what is that?
We got a couple more Timon's here.
What happens if I do this?
The expected thing happens.
Makes sense.
Okay.
Ooh, that one.
Can't quite reach that one.
Ah, but I can if I'm up there.
I see.
So we gotta open this.
Hey, what's up, Brian?
I got music for ya.
That's right.
Come here.
Thank you, buddy.
You are the best.
Okay, we're doing a Brian puzzle again.
I see the stance.
Come on then.
Chase it!
I know you wanna play with it.
No?
Why is he standing there?
Come on!
Move!
Bastard.
Do I have to waste this on you?
Oh!
Maybe I hit you with it.
Does it reach?
Not quite.
Maybe I go down here with it.
Walk the dog and then...
Oh, I should keep the button pressed.
Nah, it doesn't work, does it?
Oh, there's also a little path here.
Okay.
Pressed one of them.
How am I gonna get you...
Huh?
Maybe we hurry.
Oh, there we go!
That's right, go over there.
Look at their eyes, they're like being enchanted by it.
Hurry!
Nice!
It's a swan egg!
I like swans.
They're beautiful.
And they'll break your arm.
If you're not careful.
I respect that about them.
Um, wake up.
Okay, you're the one that likes music.
Now, am I gonna go in there first?
No, actually...
Oh!
That raises the box.
I see.
Could I not just put a slinky on that bastard and call it a day?
Ah, I'd keep slinking, of course.
So I have an idea.
Check this out.
Hey, fatty!
Follow me!
Come on!
Yes!
Follow me!
That's it!
Oh, uh...
Right.
Oh, oh, oh.
I see the problem.
Gotta be ready!
Yeah!
Sweet.
Square two lines.
Whoa!
What is going on?
Calm down!
Calm down, y'all!
Uh...
I...
Oh, off they go.
He's just as scared as I am.
Fuck, I don't know what to do here.
What is happening?
Do I...
Oh, oh!
They break my slinky!
Okay, I see the...
I... I know.
I know what to do.
Fuck off!
Oh!
Guys, come on...
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm too slow!
Okay.
Hmm.
So obviously I gotta get rid of the animals.
Uh...
Oh, go, go!
Oh, okay!
We gotta time it.
Come on, guys!
Fuck off!
Go!
Ah!
Oh, oh!
I see they instantly come back when I do it.
So we gotta wait a little bit.
Wait a little bit.
Go!
Oh, shit!
Okay, I thought I was, uh, soft-locked.
But, okay.
That's interesting.
Okay, so they're over there now.
Oh.
It's impossible.
Come on.
No!
Dude, okay.
I don't know.
Reset, reset.
So right now, there's nobody here.
But if I do this...
They instantly come running.
No.
They instantly...
They come back so fast.
I mean, their eyes light up with...
Chase the slinky.
Oh!
Yes!
Oh, that was close!
That was so close.
Um...
Oh, wait.
What?
Oh!
Maybe I need to, uh...
So slinky...
Wait, we're gonna wait for them to go away.
Okay.
Here.
Come here.
Chase it.
I mean, it's working?
Yeah!
Come here!
Ah-ha!
Bitches!
Get outplayed!
Outplayed by the yo-yo.
Easy.
That goes up.
Okay.
I think we gotta slinky some stuff here.
So, slinky down.
It's gonna...
Plop.
It's gonna plop.
Uh...
Ah!
I see.
Maybe.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
I understand.
Ah!
Too slow!
Shit.
Ah, fuck!
Haha!
I almost had it!
Okay.
Ah!
Sick!
That was awesome.
I love this game.
Okay, we have a...
What is that?
An evil fairy on the left?
And a rhinoceros.
Wait, that's Brian!
Haha!
It looks so weird with the pixels.
Oh, these are happy faces and sad faces.
Wait, what?
Maybe he likes certain music more than other music.
And we can...
This is like a legend for telling us what music he likes and what he doesn't like.
Oh, shit.
We got vines.
Oh, I see, I see, I see.
There's a hole.
Come here, buddy!
Come here, come here.
It's almost like I'm hypnotizing him with the way it's swinging back and forth like a clock.
Maybe that's the intention there.
It's really funny.
Walk the dog!
Hey!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm going up here.
You know what?
We take a picture of this.
That's right.
Take a picture of it, and we're gonna put it in our notes.
Right there.
This seems important for later, you know?
This right here.
Okay.
Go.
Let's go, buddy!
I'm trying to understand what's going on with those smiley faces.
There we go.
It's open.
Wait.
Is that a hint for something?
That confuses Brian.
I'm sorry, Brian.
I didn't mean to.
Maybe we need to use the fireworks on the smiley faces.
I don't know why, but it's just the fact that they put it there next to the fireworks, you know?
Makes me think that maybe that's what we have to do.
Okay, well, that's nice.
Making big progress.
Oh!
I wonder what this means.
Like, what's going on?
There we go.
Uh, Paraguay!
Come here.
I'm gonna hit you with the thing.
Oh, you mad now?
You mad?
Oh!
They're here, so you can't do that.
Bastard.
That's their whole purpose, is to prevent you from doing this.
Makes sense.
Now, what about the central part there?
I wanna...
Go inside.
Can I not?
Wait a minute, we still need one button.
Oh!
Shit!
I see!
Wait, did I?
Ah!
Of course, of course.
Completely forgot about this one.
Oh, what?
There we go.
Okay, that button's gonna open this elevator.
100%.
Or, it's actually a flapjack.
Oh!
Oh, I see.
Here we go!
Oh!
Ah!
No, not like that!
Where was I?
Oh, no.
I can't believe I've done this.
I was just taking it in!
I wasn't ready for a fight!
Whatever that was.
Get the yo-yo out!
Eat this!
Eat this guy!
That's right!
Oh, you don't like that, do you?
Yeah!
Eat it!
Sucker!
Wah!
Your eyes are not doing too well, are they?
Okay.
Oh, shit!
Fuck!
It's a one-hit kill!
Okay, it's personal.
I've had it with this guy.
Thinking he's all that...
He ain't shit.
Let me seduce you!
With my...
Wait, what?
No!
What?
I guess I can seduce the little guys!
That's kinda interesting.
A little interesting.
Isn't it?
Alright, fine.
Bro!
I'm not good at this game.
I'm not!
It's just how it is.
Okay, I'm gonna try and run towards him now instead of jumping.
Okay, that's actually way easier.
I can't eat.
Okay, that's better.
Ah!
Alright, sure.
Do your thing.
I don't give a shit.
Ah!
Eat it!
Mmm!
Delicious, eh?
Oh my god!
I was just standing still like an idiot.
But now I know how to do it.
I know how to do it now.
It's easy.
Easy.
Come on.
Wham!
Warm.
God, I love that sound.
It's so good.
I wish my tongue would make that sound whenever I would eat little things like this.
Ah shit, I should have made him eat it.
Hey bitch!
Okay.
Can I destroy those?
Oh my god.
I got hit.
Try again, try again.
Do it again.
Oh, fuck.
Fucking shit.
It's insane.
Okay, that's...
One down.
Easy.
One more.
No!
Your tongue doesn't work like that.
Bullshit.
No tongue goes vertical.
Fucking vertical tongue.
Cannot believe that.
Having a new strategy.
I'm gonna let him eat twice and then watch this.
Ah, okay, whatever.
Here come the eyeballs.
Oh!
Okay, good.
Ah, shit.
Okay, good, good, good.
You eat this, eat this!
Yeah!
Okay, that was way too hard for me.
That should not have been that...
hard.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
That was super easy.
Like, what is wrong with me?
Before I go here...
You guys are back, eh?
That's right!
You belong to me now!
My little mini-mees!
March!
Stop!
Oh, they fall off!
Ha-ha!
He-hey!
That would have been bad for me, actually, during that fight, but...
Oh, I broke it with my...
V-flame.
Vertical flame.
Or very flame.
That's very flame.
What am I looking at here?
Why is there a huge insect in the background?
There's four of them.
No, except that one.
The wings!
What's with the wings?
Well...
We did that!
Let's see here.
It does look like there's more up here, but...
How to get up there is the question.
Oh!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I thought that was a wall.
Oh wait, I've been here already.
I'm a dumbass.
That's not new.
Haha.
Right, then we had this place.
I'm not sure I should do anything else here.
Why is this phone looking so weird?
This phone is different than the other phones.
Is that a signifier that this is the phone I saved at?
Maybe it is.
This is definitely a skull, by the way.
What happens to the bubble?
The bubble is unaffected by the evil.
Okay.
I should fill that bubble with...
Hydrogen.
And then, uh, you know.
Flick a match up there.
Blow everything to smithereens.
Okay, so I can jump down here.
Oh, I know what to do, dude.
Oh, no.
I can't.
They saw me coming with that one.
Shit.
Oh, no.
Where am I going?
Oh, wow.
Oh, actually.
Wait, why can't I...
I have...
Oh, maybe it's a specific flame.
Oh, it is.
Oh, yeah, it is.
It's the...
Lizard thing.
Oh, man.
What is it doing?
We okay now?
Oh, you asshole.
You asshole.
Come on.
Why do I have an extra heart?
What did I do to deserve such a treatment?
Like a good treatment.
It was a good treatment.
They gave me a good treat.
I think I want to go up here now and investigate this little circle I made.
Just a little bit more.
Because apparently...
Oh, yeah, look at this.
Right here.
Uh...
Yeah.
That's an easy path.
I'm gonna grab this.
And we go right and up.
Did I mark this path?
I did.
Okay.
Or tube.
Now we go straight up.
Ah, but the question is...
How?
Wow.
That looks like a flapjack to me.
Can I face through it?
I can't.
Okay.
Save the game.
I didn't mean to jump in the water.
But a bath is good.
So in order to get up there...
No doubt I have to hit that button.
But to hit that button, I have to be up there.
So to get up there, we may have to use these pipes.
On the right.
Let's check that out again.
I know you're angry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, right.
It only goes down, eh?
Okay.
Oh, wait, what?
A chest just like that, okay.
Surely I can bubble my way here, right?
Nothing to stop me now!
No stinking birds shall ruin my uprising.
Because I am indeed rising up.
I've been in the muck for too long.
It is time to go to the top.
Oh!
Shit.
Where the sun shines...
Oh no.
No, not all the way down!
Nooooo!
Fuck off with that.
I was feeling it.
Oh my god.
Give it another try.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
That's a long way up.
This is gonna be painful to do every time we fail that.
I hear a dog?
Not that one.
That was a bird.
By the way, the right side has something.
Check it out.
I also saw stuff on the way down, by the way, on the left.
Didn't quite see what it was, but there was something there.
Oh!
Ah!
Fuck!
I was so sure I could enter that!
You kidding me?
Okay, that is... that is a bait.
That's a bait right there.
Cue Tom Hardy in that...
scene, you know?
You know what I'm talking about.
All right, little buddy, come here.
Up we go.
Actually, wait a minute.
I can totally make it up there.
Wait a sec.
This is doable.
Is it?
Maybe not.
No.
It's not doable.
Never mind.
But wait, let me try and...
Ah.
Okay.
Well...
We try again.
Focus.
Eeeeeeasy!
Where the hell am I?
What?!
This makes no fucking sense.
I am confused.
How are we down here?
Oh, you little asshole!
It's not letting me pass!
Okay.
It's gonna be like that, huh?
And you like yo-yos?
Bitch!
Oh my god, you're so annoying!
I could break you in half.
Hey, you like that?
Piss off.
I cannot believe this.
What a little POS.
Wow, you're just immune to everything, eh?
Are you immune to my sick skateboarding skills?
Oh shit, you are!
Do you have an upper limit?
An upper flight ceiling?
Doesn't look like it.
Oh my god.
What?!
How can you do this to me?
After all my work ascending...
Oh, so...
Wait, we have a...
We have an insect in the background.
Antennas!
Huge antennas!
And eyes!
Actually kinda looks like a gas mask.
A little bit.
That's weird.
Now, on the way down...
I saw some stuff.
God fucking dammit.
Anyway, I couldn't access anyway, but on the way down we saw some things.
So...
Oh, probably here.
Right there.
Let's go investigate.
Let's put our detective's hats on.
Open up those notebooks.
Put our flip phones on mute.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Doesn't even make any sense.
Something's up here for sure.
Wait, I don't think I've actually tried going up here now that I have the...
The bee wand.
Oh, yeah!
Sweet egg!
That feels good.
Not what I was looking for though.
Or was it?
Was that what I saw when I fell?
I'm not sure actually.
I guess I can fall again.
Can I fall through here as well?
Oh, no.
Okay, you can't fall here.
Oh.
I thought this was a hole.
Interesting.
This guy has been mapped.
I want to take a look at the drop again.
That's the sound you make.
That's how stupid you sound.
Dumbass.
Now...
How am I getting up?
Okay, so watch this.
Reverse!
I say!
No.
No reversement here.
We gotta find the animal, the prairie dog responsible for the...
For the downdraft here.
Let's go slow.
And really see what's going on down there.
Here we go.
It's very slow.
Calm descent.
Button.
We got a button.
And there's a ladder.
And it's right there!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Ha ha ha!
Okay, I see.
Say no more, fam.
I gotcha.
Say no more.
Gotta get to the elevator.
Boink, boink, boink.
Ah, I always do this.
Such a long path!
Oh my god!
Okay.
Down.
Not here!
I'm just gonna keep holding right.
There we go.
Wait, no.
This...
This is not quite it, is it?
We're not there yet.
Here it is.
Ah ha!
Opens the door.
On the right side.
Okay.
And to get there...
We use the pipe...
Wait, where am I?
Oh, I'm here, okay.
Now, to get over there...
Don't I just walk?
I can totally walk here...
Go up, and then left?
That seems doable.
I even have a ladder.
I remember this spot.
The atmosphere here is immaculate.
Oh.
Okay then.
Eat that.
What?
That's a bear.
In the back there.
What?
On a boat.
And kangaroos.
Wait, where is this?
This?
Okay.
Oh.
I can get to that!
I know how to get there.
In fact, while I have that fresh in my mind...
Let's investigate it.
Oh, no you're not!
You bastard!
No!
Okay, but surely you're not gonna do it from all the way up there, huh?
Oh, you...
Oh my god!
Alright, bring out the disc!
You can even jump the ladder.
The disc is coming out!
Uh, so I'm here.
So we jump down now.
And then, we hope...
Oh, but there's vines everywhere!
That's not gonna be possible!
I need to, uh, discombobulate you!
Will that work, actually?
It won't.
Okay.
What if I break your legs?
You absolute bastard.
God, he's such a buzzkill!
I was onto something!
And then he ruined it.
Cannot believe it.
Anyway...
I'm gonna go up now.
Oh shit.
There we go.
Is that gonna let me fall?
Nope, it's not.
Wait a sec, how does...
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I'm wrong here, I'm wrong.
This ladder is what I need.
Here it is.
And then straight across.
And something glorious will happen.
Hopefully.
Wait, what?
What was the point of this?
What?
That can't be real.
Okay, for sure we're gonna be able to destroy these blocks.
Remember how I called it early?
I'm still sure.
These blocks can be removed.
Somehow.
Some way.
Oh, I see now.
So, when you keep eating when you're full, you get extra hearts.
But you need a lot of them.
What?
Oh, right.
Okay, so I'm here now.
Do I wanna be here?
Or am I done being here?
There's also this spot there that's kind of intriguing.
Right there.
Maybe I'll check that out?
Um...
We're back.
And then...
Let's see.
What's easiest?
I don't... I don't know.
Where'd this one go again?
Right.
I don't wanna...
Oh, actually.
Maybe I do wanna investigate this part again.
Cause apparently there's a, um...
What's it called?
Another combination somewhere in this region, right?
It's gotta be.
Uh...
Save.
Save the game.
And now we can exit.
There we go.
Next time I'm gonna try and find that combination and we're gonna rescue all the cats.
And it'll be great.
It took a bit of time for me to get back into the game today after having a week break on this.
But once I got into the rhythm of it, I was feeling it again.
Man, this game is frickin' fantastic.
Like, I already liked it last time, but now I love it.
The drawing on the map part really sold me.
Like, that is such a huge thing for me.
Also, the...
The areas and the puzzles are just...
Phenomenal.
The pencil is...
Peak.
When we continue, uh...
I don't know.
Soon-ish.
Uh...
1B Whistler.
I...
Have some, yeah.
Not too many.
But they're definitely present.
Good to have you.
It is a great game, yeah.
It feels extremely...
Polished.
Like, it's like...
It's a complete package, you know?
Everything just works.
It's beautiful.
The music is incredible.
Very atmospheric.
Good exploration.
And the pencil, of course.
Just incredibly polished.
Yeah.
Well thought out as well.
Get it?
Yeah, and 30 megabytes!
How?
I don't understand.
Like, I...
I'm assuming, like, all the sounds...
Like, they are simple sounds.
I'm assuming they're...
They're gotta be...
Generated by code, right?
Programmatically.
It's gotta be something like that.
Otherwise...
You can't have sound files...
Lying around like that.
That's gonna take up space.
He made his own engine from scratch?
Really?
Oh yeah, the physics.
Yeah.
Super satisfying, but also simple.
Which is good.
Simple but effective physics.
It just works.
Sounds are analog?
Yeah, okay.
I can't believe he made his own engine.
Billy Basso.
What a Chad.
The sounds can be very compressed, and with all the filtering and reverb, it still sounds great.
Oh!
That's a good point, actually.
I guess so.
I mean, if you have a sound file that's essentially just...
8-bit music, or whatever.
I guess it can be very small in size.
Touching Grass was incredible, FreePancakeMan.
Why does your name sound like, uh...
What someone would call themselves if they were trying to abduct children?
You know, get in the van vibes, is what I'm getting from that name.
The sound is apparently the biggest part of the game's size.
That doesn't surprise me.
The visuals themselves, you can definitely imagine being small.
There's not a lot of pixels on each screen, right?
When I say screen, I mean, like, area screen.
Like, compared to a modern photograph taken on an iPhone or something, it's like nothing.
Hey, I'm an adult, and I would get into a van for pancakes.
Hey, good point.
Man, I haven't had pancakes in a while, but I'm actually on a health streak right now.
And I'm gonna keep it up.
I feel so good, lately, because of that.
The break did me wonders.
It was not just a break from gaming and computers.
It was also, like, a health thing, you know?
Blueprints?
Yeah, blueprints tonight.
Yep.
I was almost confused watching Wasp when people would spam the...
Oh, the road...
Oh!
I know what you mean now by the LOL.
Yeah, apparently that's just LOL.
I don't know how it ended up in the emojis.
But it's just there now, and it's here to stay, it seems.
It's kind of funny.
I am eating microwave potatoes.
Not tonight, though.
Tonight I'm having leftovers.
I made a...
Oh, what's the name?
Chorizo potato cream soup.
With green kale.
It's incredible.
And I made, like, such a huge batch.
I've been eating of it over three days now.
There's still food left.
It's incredible.
Yeah, it's really good.
With garlic, onions, and, you know...
Thyme, stuff like that.
Do you put white beans in that?
I don't.
Like, I always thought that people were being judgmental, but I see it completely differently now that I know that people are typing LOL.
What were you assuming that meant beforehand, though, Whistler?
Like, what did you assume the rodent meant with the fan in the background?
How is that a judgmental symbol for you in a...
Like, I don't understand.
Garlic, onions, and thyme.
Proceeding the concept of thyme.
I am.
It's delicious.
It smells like the past childhood.
It tastes like the future.
And it feels like the moment.
The present.
I've been eating the same batch of chili for a week now.
That sounds awesome.
That's what I do, too, when I make chili.
Just a huge batch of it.
And then I like to vary it a little bit.
Like, on some days, I get bored of just eating the chili.
Then I'll buy some tortillas.
Put them in that, you know?
Or maybe some tacos, put them in that, or...
You can eat it in so many ways.
Was that PureRef with OBS things?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was just a...
Let me see here.
I can explain it.
I'm gonna switch scenes so you can see it better.
So I can see it.
So it's just a, um...
God, what is it called?
A window capture in OBS.
And whenever I show it, it's just a simple little animation to expand it.
And I just put some filters on it to make it look better.
That's all it is.
And the inside is just...
It's just PureRef.
In the window capture.
That's it.
It took me like 50 minutes to set up.
Super easy.
And it looks nice too, right?
It fits the game.
Have some cheese on it?
Oh yeah, cheese of course.
Yeah.
Definitely.
I did not get the audio mixer yet.
I mean, I'm doing fine without it right now.
And I'm always so hesitant to buy a new thing.
Like a technology thing.
That I'd have to learn and, you know, understand.
And there's gonna be bugs with it when I set it up properly.
And it's gonna be a headache.
Oh, I'm just not wanting to do it right now.
Thank you for forcing me to buy Outer Wilds.
I didn't force anyone to buy Outer Wilds.
10 hours in and I'm already loving it.
It's so good, man.
But I'm glad you bought it.
Because it's a great game and the developers deserve a lot of money for that.
It is so worth it.
If you love puzzle games at all, Outer Wilds is a must play.
People always talk about ads.
What if there was an ads command for mods to start them whenever there's a break?
I do try to start them when there's a break.
I forget sometimes.
And I guess I haven't had a break in the last three hours.
Ish.
Maybe two and a half.
I should have taken one more break actually, but I didn't.
Usually I run ads during that.
Otherwise, there's just automatic ads playing at random.
I don't really control that.
I can only control the amount of ads.
But I also gotta earn a living, right?
So I tried to find a sweet spot, I guess.
I have watched Shawshank Redemption.
It's one of my favorite movies.
It's really good.
But then again...
When I say favorite movies, I mean top 100.
Because I have 100 favorite movies.
They're all...
There's so many good movies.
I'm watching Sense8 right now though.
The TV show.
And so far, it's kind of interesting.
It's a little cringy at times.
But if you can get past that, it's actually pretty good.
Top three movies, I can give you top two.
Black Swan is number one.
Contact is number two.
Third, I don't know.
That's a toss up between maybe 50 movies.
No, no, no.
No emote spam for breaks.
It's not like I forgot to take a break.
I just wanted to keep playing, you know?
I have played The Witness, but I got stumped by a puzzle for so long.
And I just didn't really continue it.
And it was before I started streaming.
So I never completed it because of that.
But I got pretty far.
I got really far in the game.
But there was one puzzle I just...
I could not figure it out.
So I kind of put it down for a bit, you know?
But then I forgot about it, and then I lost interest a little bit.
But I definitely did most of the things in that game.
Thoughts on rye bread?
I love it.
I love rye bread.
I eat it all the time.
You can put so many different things on it, it's incredible.
We'll keep the brake spamming to when it's 35 degrees in Denmark and you're getting delirious.
That's...
That's a deal.
That sounds good.
It's so good not being delirious anymore, man.
In fact, my feet were cold today.
Which is really nice for a change.
Even though I hate feet, cold feet, but...
Just not sitting here, you know, having fever dreams is the best.
You should play The Looker.
It's a parody of The Witness and it's great.
Okay.
A parody of The Witness?
What?
How does that work?
I guess I'll check it out one time.
I should get some next time I visit Denmark.
See if it's any different from what I get in Oslo.
I think it's pretty much the same, Whistler.
If I were to guess.
Maybe there's a bit of variation in the combination of ingredients we use, but we pretty much use the same ingredients, I think.
I don't know.
Do you have Leopostai up there?
The liver pate?
Maybe that's the thing that's a little bit more Danish.
I'm not sure.
But then again, maybe you eat that too.
I don't know.
Yeah, Leopostai.
There it is.
That one is so good with red beets.
Red beets?
Are they called red beets?
I think so.
Either that or cucumber, of course.
That's the classic.
Leopostai enjoys rise up.
Eat it with pickles?
I've never actually done that.
Pickles?
Huh.
I mean, it's just cucumbers, but pickled.
If you think...
I guess it depends on the type.
There's different variations on it.
Okay, speaking of food, I gotta go eat, man.
I'm so hungry right now.
And I'm gonna put out blueprints for those that wanna watch that.
So it's good to be back.
Thank you all for joining me.
Hanging out and subscribing.
I've seen the list of subscribers here.
Thank you very much, everybody.
It's really cool.
I feel great.
I hope you do too.
Have a wonderful Monday.
Alright?
I'll see you in the next stream slash video.
Bye bye.